{'device_name': 'Vivo Y58', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M15', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic Vs3', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Blue 20', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF (interpolated to 50 MP) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (interpolated to 8 MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme AIOS'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X6b', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F27 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G85', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 40 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HMD XR21', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic V Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 70', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Realme UI 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic V3', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X100s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + OriginOS 4'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 10 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE4 Lite (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K12x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 70x', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Realme UI 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord 4', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Flip', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X100 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 200 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + OriginOS 4'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 6 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 501', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y18e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 6', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 60', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 50 XL', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X7b 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 50 SE', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot A10', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 50 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y18', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C65', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Skyline', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14, up to 2 major Android upgrades'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 50 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 50 XL Nxtpaper', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 40', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 3rd unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C55', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 50', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 26 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 64 MP (night vision)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo 6 SE', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Max 5', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S19 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Pura 70 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z9 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Voyage 3D', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Pocket 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (spectral)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.7 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S19', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y100t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z60 Ultra Leading', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (standard) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Atlas', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F15', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 13 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 12', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G (2024)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 9s Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y28 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V60s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F6', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F25 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Power (2024)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Pura 70 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (telephoto) + 12.5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo N63', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X6 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V60', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Itel P55T', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30 Lite 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 200 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Pura 70 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (telephoto) + 12.5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Magic 9S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M14 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X Fold 3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Pura 70', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3 Pro (India)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 30 Premier', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 200', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Nothing Phone 2a Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y38', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V40', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + FuntouchOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C61', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z9x (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 12 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola S50 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Nio Phone 2', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (portrait tele) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U652S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '18 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (macro) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Nothing CMF Phone 1', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 12 Pro (China)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Neo 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F55', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Pulse', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y18i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'itel RS4', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C51s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z9 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 12s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 14, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 30', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G64', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3 Energy Edition', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT 6T', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 16 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 18'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 12 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 14, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 9s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo 40 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Focus', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix GT 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 8a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C38', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V40 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12x (India)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Focus Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 50 Fusion', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT 6', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 50 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mix Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C65 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens/sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE 4', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T3x 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 21 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme OS'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE4 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Ridge Pro', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12x', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 50 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12 4G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Civi 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U24 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 13 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Enjoy 70z', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme P1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 60 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z8x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 12 F', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C61', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M55', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + One UI 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme P1', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Turbo 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 6', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP (wide) + Cover camera: 10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X100s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + OriginOS 4'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 70 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Realme UI 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Skyline', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 12i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 14 + no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Vibe', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V40 SE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + FuntouchOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X Fold 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Polestar Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Polestar OS'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 6 RSR Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 180 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mix Fold 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 10 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 40 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 200 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 6 Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 180 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'HMD Pulse Pro', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M6 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y03', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A60', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X60i', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K12', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 9S Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C63', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 20P', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 14 Civi', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo N65', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens/sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi A3x', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 40 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 VI', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M35', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1 VI', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 8', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview Oscal Tiger 12', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Doke OS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 30', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord 30 SE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (micro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 8', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord 20 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'OxygenOS 14.0.0.300'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 13', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Poco X6 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 30 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP + 32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Nothing Phone (2a)', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A79', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A15', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP + 32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Itel P55 5G', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S18 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 64 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Yuva 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Auxiliary lens'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 12 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A15 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 100 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Itel P55', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.8 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 11F 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 11x', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S18', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 11 F', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A25', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic V2 RSR Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 20 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C67 4G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot KingKong 8', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 12 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (telephoto) + 60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 70', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{"device_name": "OnePlus Open", "manufacturer": "OPPO", "rear_camera": {"resolution": "48 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)"}, "front_camera": {"resolution": "20MP, f/2.2, 20mm (ultrawide), 1/4.0\", 0.7µm, Cover camera: 32MP, f/2.4, 22mm (ultrawide), 1/3.14\", 0.7µm"}, "operating_system": "Android 14"}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M6 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 100', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G84', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (market/region dependent)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T2 2023', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Note 21', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 13R Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X7b', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 8\u2009MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 11 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 23 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 64 MP (night vision)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G54 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 50 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V50 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 14 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 60x', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X6', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14, planned upgrade to Android 14, HyperOS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 20', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee V30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 20 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A59', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + ColorOS 13.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A38', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + ColorOS 13.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 8 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 0.8 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power Armor 18T Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (FLIR thermal camera, Lepton module)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 12', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14 (International), OriginOS 4 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A2x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M6', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 21', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 5 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Flyme 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Storm', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y100 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 505', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Hi Enjoy 60s', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate X5', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0 (China), EMUI (Europe), no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K70', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A18', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi 12R', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP33 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 20 MP (night vision) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K70 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL 6x', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y27s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A55', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi A3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 40 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 24', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 64 MP (night vision)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 60 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64\u2009MP (periscope telephoto) + 8\u2009MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V50', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + HyperOS'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 20 Classic', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Flyme 10'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL 6x Pro', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview Shark 8', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Yuva 3', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z60 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (standard) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 12', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Fairphone 5', 'manufacturer': 'FIIL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Planned upgrade to Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide),'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y36m', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (telephoto) + 60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y78t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G04', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 9 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide),'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y100i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A05s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom V Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 32 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y36i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X50i Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 9 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno11 Pro (China)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP + 32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X9b', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A05', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5 V', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G24 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z8 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 13C', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 40 NxtPaper 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 20C', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C65', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 40 NxtPaper', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad CP12s', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer U683S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (macro) + 0.03 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'NIO Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'SkyUI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y200 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT5 240W', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 20 MP (night vision) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C67 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 8T', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G34 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 60 RS Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze 2 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Note 40', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y12 (4G)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y17s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y27 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + ColorOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 12R', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic Vs2', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 20 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N30 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (micro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V50s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'itel S23+', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova Y72', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X7 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + ColorOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C36', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'itel A70', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X40 GT Racing', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 6', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 32 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Itel P55 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A35', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 13R', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 21 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Flyme 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 13 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X8b', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MagicOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K70e', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G24', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark Go 2024', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Note 50', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 8', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 13C 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 90 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo G2', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP + 50\u2009MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Play (2024)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 11 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP + 32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G54', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F25', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50\u2009MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 11 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S18e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 70 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 40S', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace 3', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 20 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (auxiliary lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 40C', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X50 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V29e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y77t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find N3 Flip', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K60 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C210', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G310', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 40', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT5', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 11', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel Fold', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 10.8 MP (telephoto) + 10.8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 11i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T2x (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F23 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo T2 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F23 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire E2 Play', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo N53', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 10 Pro Global', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12R Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android + MIUI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S23 FE', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Upgradable to Android 14)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 11S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire E3 lite', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A14 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 30i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 60X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 10 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y11 (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V29 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Nothing phone (2)', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Agni 2', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 12', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (ultrawide) + 64 MP (periscope)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S24', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 10 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Fold', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 30', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V29 Lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 60', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 20 MP (periscope telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y78', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo 6', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y27', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire E Star', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 7', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z50S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (standard) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'iQOO Neo 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 32 MP + 50 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A72s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 13T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U23', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia N5', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 13 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 7 Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy XCover 6 Pro Tactical Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A98 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V29', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 16 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 20', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C53 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus K11', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S23 Pro Tactical Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Y71', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 12, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Red Magic Gaming Tablet', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (portrait) + 60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F34', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Reno 10 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview Active 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Yuva 2', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 8S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide),'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix GT 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Y91', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 13T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 8S Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide),'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N30 5G 2023', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (micro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 11', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 11RT', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 21', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 24 MP (night vision)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14 for POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y36 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi K60 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A78 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'POCO F5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 30', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V70', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 5', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y36 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 8', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F5', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13 POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 20', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme 10'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X6a', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP (wide) + Cover camera: 10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'POCO F5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 10', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 20 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z7s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S17t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y78 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 60', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Realme UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 20 Premier', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 108 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 20 Infinity', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme 10'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 15 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 17'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X50i', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y35 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 17'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze 2', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find N3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Realme UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S17e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 17'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X50', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z60 Fold', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 90 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 40 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X Fold 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X90s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y35m Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 10', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 15', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 17'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Power 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 40', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U23 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mix Fold 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y78m', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 14 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y02T', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C53', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 7T', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 12 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X100 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP + 16 MP + 64 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 40', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 7T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C51', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus V Fold', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C110', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 7', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + other unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 14', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X100 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14 (International), OriginOS 4 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 90 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 11 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12R', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 90', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 10', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 10C', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 11 4G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X100', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 64 MP + 50 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14 + Funtouch 14 (International), OriginOS 4 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova Neo 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + Secondary unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 30i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 12', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C300', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo N55', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (micro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 5', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic V2', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 20 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge Plus (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F54', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 64 MP + 48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '11 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G14', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A58 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + ColorOS 13.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi A2+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C12 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 50 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50  MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus 5G (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M34 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 V', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y02A', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 8', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 14'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze 1X', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 11 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (portrait) + 60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G42', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Neo', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1 V', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 11 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C51', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia XR21', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y36 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 7 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 0.8 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot KingKong Star', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 24 MP (night vision camera) 2 IR emitters + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot KingKong 9', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 24 MP (night vision camera) 2 IR emitters + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV8900', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP, thermal assisted camera + FLIR thermal camera (Lepton module)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 30 VIP', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S17', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K11x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo 5 SE', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Yuva 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Reno 9 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 405', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X90 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X90', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro Speed', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P60', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.1 (China) + EMUI (Europe), no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X6', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + ColorOS 13.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C55', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A17k', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K60E', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P60 Art', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 48 MP (telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.1 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y56', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V21s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi A2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 20S', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 11A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT3', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (microscope)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 20 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50.3 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y100', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme 10'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 2023', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee V Max', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 20 MP (night vision) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M14', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 11', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 60', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power Armor 19', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 6C', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V27e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 11', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A34', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V27', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 13', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X40 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X40', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M54', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + One UI 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE 3', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X9a', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + ColorOS 13.1'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find N2 Flip', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V27 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + Funtouch 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X7a', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S96 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP + 20 MP (night vision) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A54', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X8a', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Magic UI 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate X3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.1 (China), EMUI (Europe)'}
{'device_name': 'TCL Ion X', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Yuva Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 13 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide), under display'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 8 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide), under display'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V40 Design', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MyOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A56s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 4', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + other unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview Oscal S80', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Doke-OS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 80 Pro Flat', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '160 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X90 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50.3 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Voyage 40 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MyOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G52L', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP (macro) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 12 Discovery Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + other unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 40 Ultra Space Edition', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 64 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo 5', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V40', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S16e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Play (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X5', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V30', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z50 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo 5 240W', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A98', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 7 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E32 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 10', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A14 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 10 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + unspecified MP (telephoto) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace 2V', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S16', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO U6', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find N2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + Cover camera: 32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 20i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 7', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K60', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 + MIUI 14'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8T', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (microscope) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.5, (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X5', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 20', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze Nxt', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 10 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30 XL', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + TCL UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G72 Max', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S16 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y02', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C55', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A85', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y55s (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 10 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 408', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12 (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic Vs Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Cloned – Oppo Reno 8T', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (microscope) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire E Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 5 Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 40 SE', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12 Lite NE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 20 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G23', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 80 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 80 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola ThinkPhone', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A58', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y73t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Y61', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko 10', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A04e', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A14', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 12C', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 70 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 5', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 40R', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + TCL UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 40 SE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5  MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MyOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C50', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 11R', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M04', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C22', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Pocket S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.7 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 40 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F04', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C32', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G22', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E13', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S75', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 80', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '160 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z7x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'iQOO Neo 8', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Defy 2', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 7 Racing', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 20', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 80 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '160 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth).'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G13', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom V Fold', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'iPhone 15', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 17'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z50', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z7 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 7', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark Go 2023', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace 2', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 10s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A77s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A24 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Civi 3', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 20 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C02', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y35 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z7i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 7 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power Armor 18T', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + FLIR thermal camera (Lepton module) + 5 MP (for thermal module)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 (Indian Variant)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 48 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.1 (China) + EMUI (Europe), no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 50z', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (night vision)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S23 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 7a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G53', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C12', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 10T', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Unspecified MP (telephoto) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Play (2023)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G73', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C33 2023', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI S'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V41 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A78', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F14', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom X2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S23', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S23 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 10 MP (periscope telephoto) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 30', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E22', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y77e (t1)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Civi 2', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 20 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G42', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V25', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S15', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C200', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '100 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2  MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MyOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi A1+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.08 MP (QVGA)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F13', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X8 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 19 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo3T', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 9', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G72', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X4 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T1 (Snapdragon 680)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K10 Energy', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 11s NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11R', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 14 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 16'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A97', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V40s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 10', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nothing phone (1)', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G82', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12 Pro (Dimensity)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 14.6 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V25 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G62', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 6D Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 6', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z40S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova Neo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + Secondary unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9i 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'TCL Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 7S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi A1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP primary + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 GO Edition'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z5 (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A77 (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y77', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y35', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y77e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T1x (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 40 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 64 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MyOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C31', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova Neo 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C30s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 2022', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12S Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth) sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V40 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto S30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MYUI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G71s', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 6 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G60', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y02s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K50 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12 G96', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 70', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X80 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K10x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X30', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 22 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate Xs 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.7 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 70 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X6', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion Y70', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5 IV', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 70 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '54 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 9', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Unspecified secondary camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 11', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 6 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.8 camera (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO U5e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A57e', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 32 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12 VIP', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + XOS 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M13 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Y90', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Blaze Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) camera + 2 MP (macro) + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 8 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (microscope) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E22s', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0 (China) + EMUI 12 (Europe)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 12 Play NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X40i', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11T Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (portrait) + 60 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A57s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y16', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T2x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T2', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A13 (SM-A137)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 12', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 9T', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M13', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace Racing', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X Fold+', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M5s', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X40', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z6 44W', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 6 Batman Edition', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 30 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C100', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y52t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V25e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A77 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 50 RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50 MP, f/1.4-f/4.0, 24mm (wide), PDAF, Laser AF, OIS + 48 MP, f/3.0, 90mm (periscope telephoto macro) + 13 MP, f/2.2, 13mm, 120˚ (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP, f/2.4, 18mm (ultrawide), TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor) , HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E22i', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N20 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 12i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + XOS 10.6'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 50E', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 50 MP main sensor, f/1.4-f/4.0, 24mm (wide), PDAF, Laser AF, OIS + 13 MP secondary sensor, f/2.2, 13mm, 120˚ (ultrawide), PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Single: 13 MP, f/2.4, 18mm (ultrawide), HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A57 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 6D', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12L + One UI 4.1.1'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 9T (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z6x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 11 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 IV', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y33e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y22s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G32', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 50', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 13 (International)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1 IV', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP + 0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E32s', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A04', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 13 (International)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10 Prime 2022', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11 SE (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y75s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 9 SE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + EMUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A04s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z6 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 30 Fusion', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y77 (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G400', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y22', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Y70 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'EMUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50i Prime', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M5', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C33', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI S'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 10T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'BLU F91', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F4', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13 POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K50i 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 20s', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + CoolOS 2'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A04 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 19 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 19', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 19 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 50 MP (telephoto) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G62 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M13 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A52', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP (macro) + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A72', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP (macro) + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT2 Explorer Master', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12 Ultra (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M53', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Quad: 108MP (wide) + 8MP (ultra-wide) + 2MP (depth) + 2MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X80', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 GB (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S15e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P50 Pocket', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.7 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E32', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 14 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 16'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V23 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Philips PH2', 'manufacturer': 'Philips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS + HMS (Huawei Mobile Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 14 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth).'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 16'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Origin OS Ocean'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A76', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X Fold', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 50 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 4', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Magic UI 6, Google Play Services (market/region dependent)'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi K40S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF, OIS + 8 MP, 119˚ (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4, (macro), HDR, panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, (wide) , 1080p@30/120fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F21 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 64MP + 2MP + 2MP, HDR, Panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32MP , HDR, Panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Origin OS Ocean'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V23 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G11', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + TOF 3D (depth) camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Magic UI 6, Google Play Services (market/region dependent)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G52', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax In note 2', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 14', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 16'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO U5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Origin OS Ocean'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + TCL UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21T (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10 2022', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion Y90', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ZUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G21', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi CIVI 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 11i', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5 E'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y33', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + TCL UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (microscope) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO K10', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide) + 2 MP, f/2.4, (macro) + 2 MP, f/2.4, (depth) , HDR , Panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C2 2nd Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 40', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP + 8 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + Secondary unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + HiOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T1 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30 XE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 10 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 with ColorOS 12.1 (China) - OxygenOS 12 (Global)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C30', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30 V 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 60 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + Other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C40', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C21', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP Samsung ISOCELL HM2, f/1.9, 26mm, 1/1.52, 0.7µm, PDAF; 8MP Sony IMX355 (Ultrawide), f/2.2, 118˚; 2 MP GalaxyCore GC02M1 (Macro) , f/2.4; 2 MP (Depth), f/2.4.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP SK Hynix Hi-1634Q, f/2.5, (wide), 1/3.06 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S12', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Origin OS Ocean'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT2', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + XX MP (ultrawide) + XX MP (microscope)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21a', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A55s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C21 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50A Prime', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X10', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X30', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee V20', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 20 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oneplus Nord 3', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 13'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE 2 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 12i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 8'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y33T', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark Go 2022', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30E', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 5S', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + HiOS'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V23', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oneplus Nord 2T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + OxygenOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 30 SE', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + TCL UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MyOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F4 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F21 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S100 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 20 MP (night vision), 2 infrared night vision lights + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire E2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Red Magic 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Red Magic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 64MP + 8MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP under display, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A53 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 5 RS', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Joy UI 12.8'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno7 Z 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21T', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y55 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Joy UI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Red Magic 7', 'manufacturer': 'Red Magic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 64MP (wide) + 8MP (ultra-wide) + 2MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP , HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 11 2022', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find N 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50MP (wide) omnidirectional PDAF, OIS + 13MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom, PDAF + 16MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32MP (wide) : 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 12 - Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G91 Max', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP (depth) + 3rd unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Joy UI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge S30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MYUI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 9 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + EMUI 12, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q5', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE S98', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 64MP (main) + 20MP (night vision) + 8MP (wide-angle)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50MP (wide) + 50MP (ultra-wide) + 2MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60MP (wide) or 60MP (wide) underdisplay'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'POCO X4 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 64MP + 8MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo IQOO Neo 5S', 'manufacturer': 'iQOO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 48MP (wide), OIS + 13MP (ultra-wide) + 2MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP (wide), HDR , 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 10R', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + OxygenOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Quad: 108MP (wide), PDAF, OIS + 13MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (macro) + 2MP ( depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP (wide) ,1080p@30fps, 720p@120fps, HDR, Panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50MP Sony IMX766 (ultra-clear) + 5MP (macro) + 13MP (ultra-wide-angle)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32MP , 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A23', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C35', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50 MP (wide) + 2MP (macro) + 2MP (depth), HDR, Panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP , HDR, 720p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Secondary unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X Note', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Quad: 50MP (wide), PDAF, Laser AF, OIS + 8MP (periscope, telephoto), PDAF, OIS, 5x optical zoom +12MP (telephoto), PDAF, 2x optical zoom + 48MP (ultrawide), Zeiss optics, Zeiss T* lens coating'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50MP main + 48MP +48MP + 48MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.4, 25mm (wide), 0.7µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12, MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X9', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A96', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X7', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q5i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K50 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A36', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO U5x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Origin OS Ocean'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic V', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '42 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Magic UI 6, Google Play Services (market/region dependent)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M33 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP, f/1.9, 24mm (wide) + 50 MP, f/1.9, 48mm (telephoto), 2x optical zoom + 50 MP, f/2.2, 115˚ (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32MP, HDR, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y32', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A57 (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge X30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50 MP, f/1.9, (wide) + 50 MP, f/2.2, 114˚ (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Single : 60MP f/2.2, (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Philips PH1', 'manufacturer': 'Philips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K50 Gaming Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 64MP (Wide) + 8MP (Ultra-wide) + 2MP (Macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP , HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 6T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A73', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide), 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo5 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mix 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 48 MP + 12 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X4 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13 for POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 6T', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE 2 Lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + CoolOS 2'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 50MP + 2MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 18T', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 3 MP (microscope)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 8C', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) _+ HiOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G22', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C31', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 305', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Frontier', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '194 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus 5G (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A16e', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1 Lite'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 4 Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (ultrawide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 50 MP (wide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Magic UI 6.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee G13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 6', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + QVGA + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + HiOS'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A33 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X5 Pro Dimensity Edition', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP +50 MP+13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y75 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mix Fold 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A73 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide), 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M4 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10 Prime+ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P50E', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z6', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic 4 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K50', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11S 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10C', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X8', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X80 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X80 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9 5G Speed', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 48MP (wide) + 2MP (macro) + 2MP (depth), HDR, panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP (wide), HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V21', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11 Pro+ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 15.3'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F23', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V25', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lava X2', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M23', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M33', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A13', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11E Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y33s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Origin OS Ocean'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 9 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 48MP(wide) + 2MP(macro) + 2MP(depth), HDR, panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP (wide), HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Asus 8z', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP Sony IMX686, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/1.73, 0.8µm, PDAF, OIS, 12 MP Sony IMX363, f/2.2, 112˚, 14mm (ultrawide), 1/2.55, 1.4µm, dual pixel PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP Sony IMX663, f/2.5, 28mm (standard), 1/2.93, 1.22µm, dual pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ZenUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13 for POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11E', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 13'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X100', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 30 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '200 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 20e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0 (China) + EMUI 10.1 (International), no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F19s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V23e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V11s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12.1 + OxygenOS 12.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 6 Pro 5G (Snapdragon)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.3'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Master', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X30 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 60', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic3', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, Magic UI 5, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 11s', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + Unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 6a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50A', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y15s (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 18', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C1 2nd Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y55s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X30i', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 11', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 10'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S22 Flip', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) 3.5x optical zoom, 10x hybrid zoom + 64 MP (monochrome) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, Magic UI 5, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 3 MP (microscope)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + Realme UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 50i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme Go UI'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 13 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D (depth/biometrics)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 15'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 8i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A16K', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1 Lite'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MiFavor 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 8P', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G300', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 50 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2 (Google Play Services (market/region dependent)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade L9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP (wide) + 12MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 12MP (ultrawide) sensors + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 15'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Magic3 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) 3.5x optical zoom, 10x hybrid zoom + 64 MP (monochrome) + 64 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, Magic UI 5, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 18 Premier', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F42 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI Core 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M32 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 11s', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 10'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X20', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 18 P', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S22 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia Pro-I', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y54s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola G Pure', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12 (International), OriginOS for iQOO 1.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20 R 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 6', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge X', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 50 MP +2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Microsoft Surface Duo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Microsoft', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 GB (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G31', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 5T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A54s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A16', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 18i', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + Other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G50 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G41', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Civi', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M4 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord 2 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11.3'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A56 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 13 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP (wide) + 12MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 12MP (ultrawide) sensors + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 15'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y20T', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y33s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A12 Nacho', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V30 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A95', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A13 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S22+ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G71 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play5 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 4S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Joy UI 12.8'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 4S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Joy UI 12.8'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S22 Ultra 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 10 MP (periscope telephoto) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + One UI 4'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K9s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G51 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S10', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y21s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G200 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 13', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP (Wide ) + 12MP (Ultra-wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP (Wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 15'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power Armor 14', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultra wide-angle) + 20 MP (night version) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, upgrade to Android 11 later'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 5.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 III Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 8', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + Secondary unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A55', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q3s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8 SE 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia XR20', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 0.8 camera (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y50t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E40', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 8'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 7 SE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y71t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.3'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 13P', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Fairphone 4', 'manufacturer': 'FIIL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 48 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax In 2b', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A03', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y15a', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M21 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, One UI 3.1 Core'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C25Y', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI R'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C31', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'TCL L10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Voyage 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MyOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M22', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI Core 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y3s (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9i Sport', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10T 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 11i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 20', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A71', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9A Sport', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 11 Lite 5G NE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 8s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9 Activ', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 10i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 +XOS 7.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X4 NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5 for POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 11 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 11T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V30', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G50', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo T1x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 9RT', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)+ 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + OxygenOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y53s 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K9x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 11T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 5', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + HIOS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A03 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 3 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z5x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0 for iQOO'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 6s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Redmagic 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 18s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 32 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Flyme 9'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M52 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y72 5G (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y76 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 6s', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Redmagic 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus RT', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)+ 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.X'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Reno 7 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + Unspecified + 2 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P50 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 40 MP (B/W)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero X Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo2T', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 8', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola one 5G UW ace', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 11T 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo Gaming', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge 20 Fusion', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi 11i HyperCharge', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5 E'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A52s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K13', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Smartphone for Snapdragon Insiders', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 5s', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8 SE Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V23e 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 5s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo2', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y74s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Power (2022)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G60S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C21Y', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'vivo x70', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch OS 12 (International), OriginOS 1.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Agni 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 6', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 11 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Samsung HM2 108 MP + 8 MP (Sony IMX355, ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X70 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch OS 12 (International), OriginOS 1.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z2s', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q3t', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 11', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y76s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Master Explorer', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11 Lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide) + 8 MP, f/2.2, 119˚ (ultrawide) + 5 MP, f/2.4, (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.2, 27mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S10e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G91 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno7 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E20', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (telephoto macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 11', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 11T 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F22', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI Core 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT 5G Master', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 30 Ultra 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 64 MP (standard) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 64 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MyOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F3 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oneplus Nord LE', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + OxygenOS 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + Secondary unknown camera + Third unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 Pro (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X20 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 64 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MyOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL V+ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G50', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer U680S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 2 MP + VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X7 Max 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion Duel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ZUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M3 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P50', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 7 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 30 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Quad (64 MP, Wide Angle Camera + 8 MP, Wide Angle, Ultra-Wide Angle Camera + 5 MP Camera + 5 MP, depth Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, Wide Angle Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hard Case G5', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 20 MP + 13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 11 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Carbon 1 MK II', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 16 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 5 Ultimate', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20S', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A95 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V21e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F3', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M3', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V21 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero X', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 18', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Flyme'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40E', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (biometrics sensor only)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C25s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G10 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A93s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20L', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S9e', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A03s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X60t Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20L+', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A94', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A54', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 7T', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + Secondary unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 F', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.3'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 7P', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + Secondary unspecified camera + Third unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y30G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 Z 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS V11.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X70 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 12 (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch OS 12 (International), OriginOS 1.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Quantum 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q3 Pro Carnival', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F19 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V21e 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark Go 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition) + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11i', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A35', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 6R', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Redmagic 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F19 Pro Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 20X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5 III', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) Dual Pixel PDAF, 3x/4.4x optical zoom + 12 (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate X2 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'HarmonyOS 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (ultrawide) + 0.1 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11 Global Version', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Max Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP  (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Defy (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K40 Gaming', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A74', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M42 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 18 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Flyme'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 50', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2 (Google Play Services (market/region dependent)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Redmagic 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40E 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 30A', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 Pro (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V21', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A74 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 8', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT Neo Flash', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C21', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 K', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 20', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N200 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11.X'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X60t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G20', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) +2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1L Pro (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, Funtouch 11.1 (International), OriginOS for iQOO 1.0 (China)'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '11.1 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K40 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A53s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 6', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Redmagic 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V40 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G60', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS for iQOO'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 64 MP (standard) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) and 64 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + nubia UI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A22 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI Core 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom X', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord 2', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11.X'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X60 Pro (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (portrait) 5x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y52 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U3x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS for iQOO 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (monochrome)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 1 +, XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 10 Pro NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (monochrome)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 1 +, XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (ultrawide) + 32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Magic UI 4.2,'}
{'device_name': 'Oneplus 9R', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q3i 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (monochrome)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 8 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 44 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Legion OS'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X3 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1 (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y53s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno6 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q3', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y20s [G]', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 9E', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C01 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 30', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 5T Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 6 Z', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno6 Pro+ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'LG W41', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X7 Pro Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q3 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 8 ZS673KS', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ZenUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S21 FE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) 1.1x optical zoom, 3x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G20', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'LG W41 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Fold3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.5'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 8 Flip ZS672KS', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized flip-up main camera module'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ZenUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K13 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X10', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X3 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5 for POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y12s 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F02s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG W41 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X20', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C30', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 7', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.5'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z2 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi K40 Game Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 12 base on Android 11 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12 for POCO'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A22', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI Core 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C20A', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oneplus 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G40 Fusion', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y70t', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax In 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play5 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M12 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE S30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MyOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord CE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F52 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F12', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A94 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y72 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C25', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 17P', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 4th unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 11 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultra wide-angle) + 20 MP (night version) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, upgrade to Android 11 later'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE S30 SE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MyOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (monochrome)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G100', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + TOF 3D'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 17', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 3rd unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + HIOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia G10', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 8', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ZenUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE S30', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MyOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire E3', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 8 Flip', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized flip-up main camera module'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ZenUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V13 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C11 (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme Go UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 10T', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP + Third unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 +XOS 7.6'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix Fold', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y52s t1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M32', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pova', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Joy UI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A55 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q2i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y70', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S7e 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y30 Standard', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 5a 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M02s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Q2', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K40', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Race Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 13 MP + 13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO U3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + IQOO UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K7x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unspecified camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S7t 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 16 S', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (dedicated) + 4th unknown camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7s 2020', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y20s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V15 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 20 4G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide), under display'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax In 1b', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool S', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10 Pro 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme GT 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10i 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'LG W31', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A52 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A93 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax In note 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 3 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y51a', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 5', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K12', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 SE 5G Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 8i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MiFavor 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9T 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A52 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 8i', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + XOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 9', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y20A', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C20', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A7', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 Pro Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP, (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + XOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 11P', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y20 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 10X lite', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V40 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + Color spectrum sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1 III', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) Dual Pixel PDAF, 3x/4.4x optical zoom + 12 (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q52', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee K30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A02', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG K92 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 21 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N100', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + OxygenOS 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 8T+ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y11s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y31s 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 5 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) +Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + XOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord N10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + OxygenOS 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C15 Qualcomm Edition', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S21 Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 64 MP (periscope telephoto) 1.1x optical zoom, 3x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo X 2021', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6i', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40 RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 12 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y51 (2020, December)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11, Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo X60 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 12', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F21', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2 V Tella', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (AF) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.4', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) gimbal stabilization + 13 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 12 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 14'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1S (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7a', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP + 8 MP + 13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 12, base on Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M02', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'itel A47', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Go Edition + Android Pie OS.'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A15', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20 SE', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 4G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 6 Go', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + HIOS 6.2'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F19', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F41', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, One UI Core 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V20 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40 Pro+', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 12 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M31 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Play (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy F62', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 20 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 7 (Global)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Power (2021)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M62', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 7i (Global)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View40', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + Color spectrum sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 4.0, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y3s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X8', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One 5G Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A32 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 1.4', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition), planned upgrade to Android 11 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + TOF 3D (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A53 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 40', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 8 MP (telephoto) optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (portrait) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO U1x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 12A', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X1 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) +2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V11 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A32 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Poco M3', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 50 MP (ultrawide) + 3 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 11', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco C3', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X51 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 13 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, Funtouch 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A72 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G10', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) +2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y31', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z6', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30E Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 3D TOF (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 10 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + Secondary unspecified camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + XOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A53s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A73', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10i', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart HD 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition) + XOS 6.2'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 30', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Quad (64 MP, Wide Angle Camera + 8 MP, Wide Angle, Ultra-Wide Angle Camera + 5 MP Camera + 5 MP, depth Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, Wide Angle Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A15s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 5', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Red Magic 6', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1SE (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 16', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A33 (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S21 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) 1.1x optical zoom, 3x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S21 Ultra 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 10 MP (periscope telephoto) + 10 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X60 Pro Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 32 MP (telephoto) + 48 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OriginOS 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 20 5G Extreme', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide), under display'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X7 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X50e 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, Funtouch 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate X2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 11, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y73s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y52s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V2020 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) +2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MiFavor 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V20', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 III', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Rog Phone 4', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10T Lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 20 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) +2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MiFavor 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A73 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 7 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno5 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + ColorOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8 V 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus 2021', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A12', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG W31+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A02s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M21s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, One UI Core 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y12s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E7', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M12', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G9 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M12', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 8 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1 (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X50', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A Quantum', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 8P', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10X 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco M2', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 7 ZS670KS', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized flip-up main camera module'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ZenUI 7'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Fusion', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10X Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 5S', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Redmagic 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A32', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 12 for POCO, based on Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A01 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6S', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X3 NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 12 for POCO, based on Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG Velvet 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + LG UX 9'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Fold2 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide) + Cover camera: 10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P Smart S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 10', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA (Low light sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 9.3 PureView', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10T 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A53', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z5x (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), upgradable to Android 10, Funtouch 10'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X3', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M31s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab Active3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Z', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 FE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Z1x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Fusion Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A72 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 M (depth) sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 F', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A11k', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 Z 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)+ 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G90', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y70s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S12 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M01s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI Core 1.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Fast', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M30', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 5 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 13 MP (portrait) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + IQOO UI 1.5'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C3i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'LG K31', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + LG UX 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 7', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Zero 2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y51s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 11 4G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6i (India)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C11', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V20 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) gimbal OIS + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 13 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Max', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP  (wide) + 0.3 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 4', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO 5 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 8 MP 135mm (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + IQOO UI 1.5'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 20 Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) 4x optical zoom 10x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video + 0.3 MP TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee K3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 other unknown cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP B/W (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO U1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG Wing 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X50 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 9E', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Fairphone 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'FIIL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C17', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X10 Max 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 6', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP 120˚ (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9C', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 8', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion Duel', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Legion OS/ ZUI12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A72', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + One UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30i', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9i', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.4', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, planned upgrade to Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) 1.1x optical zoom, 3x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 3 Strix', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP + 64 MP + Unknwon'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Single Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9C (NFC)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A21s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X3 SuperZoom', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10T Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 9', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + FLIR thermal camera (Lepton module 2.5+5MP, f/2.4)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A71s 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q92 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 SE', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G9 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 8', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide), under display'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Spark 6', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 5G Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + nubia UI 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 11 SE 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MiFavor 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note20 Ultra 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom, 50x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus Nord', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5MP (depth) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K7 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A51 5G UW', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 20 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 12 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom, 50x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'LG K52', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 12 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.4 (wide) + 12 MP f/2.0 (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 12 MP f/2.4 (ultrawide) cameras + TOF 3D LiDAR scanner (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + SL 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 14 (upgradable to iOS14.7)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C12', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Spark Power 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + QVGA (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom, 30x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G9 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + QVGA + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C15', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S1 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 7i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 3', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ROG UI'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X50 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 13 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 5', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Microsoft Surface Duo', 'manufacturer': 'Microsoft', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '11 MP (Wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Uses main camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A93', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4a 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C2 Tennen', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 FE 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 10A', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5 II', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 16 Premier', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated video camera) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Spark 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 3', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+13MP+8MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 7.0 base on Android'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S62 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + FLIR thermal camera (Lepton 3.5 module)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C2 Tava', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V19 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y20i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F17', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA (Low light sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 64 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom, 30x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A12s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 5G Racing', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C5 Endi', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y20', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'LG K62', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '28 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 SE', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 7 Pro ZS671KS', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized flip-up main camera module'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ZenUI 7'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 48 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom with 120x hybrid zoom + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 8T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11 + OxygenOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy Z 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.4', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, planned upgrade to Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A42 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X3', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50 Pro Player', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X7', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y8p', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V3', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 20', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9a', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 32 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Flyme 8.1'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 20A', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'LG K42', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y30', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme V5 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG K71', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y8s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1 (with Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S7 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (portrait) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Funtouch 10.5'}
{'device_name': 'Honor X10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Spark 5 Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 Pro New Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) 5x optical zoom 10x hybrid zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10, EMUI 10.1, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno4', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + + 2 MP (macro) 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco F2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (telephoto macro) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5p', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 9P', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6p', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10 with HMS (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Velvet 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + LG UX 9'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M21', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (biometrics sensor only)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'LG K51S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG K41S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, (wide) + 5 MP, (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO Neo 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) Periscope (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9X Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Legion', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Legion OS'}
{'device_name': 'Poco F2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Poco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Power Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP + QVGA low light camera sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 8S 2020', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + Periscope 48 MP (telephoto), 1/2.0, 0.8µm, PDAF, OIS, 10x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) AF, Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M01', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire R70', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, (wide) + 2 MP, (macro) + 2 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A52', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro ) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C3', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A21', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 Pro Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 17', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Flyme 8.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A12e', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + ColorOS 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Z Flip', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A12', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M11', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) 5 Mp (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10; Magic UI 3.1, no Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q51', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Poco X2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Play', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + nubia UI 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A31', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A92', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro ) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A31', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo NEX 3S 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 4T', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M51', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + iQOO UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 4T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Lite Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (periscope telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V19', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Core (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8A Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 20e', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 3 other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8A Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 11 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M31', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A71 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9900 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+5MP+16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S5 lite', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP + AI Lens (low light sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); XOS 5.5'}
{'device_name': 'LG Velvet', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (standard)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + LG UX 9'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, (wide), Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP, (telephoto), PDAF, OIS, 3x optical zoom + 12 MP, (ultrawide), AF, Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 15', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 3 other unspecified cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 9S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Ace 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W (depth) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X6', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Youth 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 12'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 15 Premier', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + HIOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 7E', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide)+ 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1 II', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom, OIS + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Pro Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '52 MP (wide) Periscope (telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 8A Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z71', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP (telephoto) PDAF, OIS, 3x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 8', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) (OIS+EIS) + 16MP Ultra Wide + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, (wide), Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP, (telephoto), PDAF, OIS, 3x optical zoom + 12 MP, (ultrawide), AF, Super Steady video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 Vitality', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 10X 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30S', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS); Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1B (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10 with HMS (no Google Play Services)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 lite New Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 A', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide), 5 MP, (ultrawide) + 2 MP, (macro) 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 II', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) PDAF, 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A51 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7p', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30i 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate Xs', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No - uses main camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + EMUI 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS + 64 MP (telephoto) PDAF, OIS, 3x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) AF Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Red Magic 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Redmagic 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 Pro Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '50 MP (wide) omnidirectional + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 10x optical zoom + 8 MP (telephoto)3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D(depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + IR TOF 3D, (depth/biometrics sensor)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) omnidirectional PDAF, Laser AF, OIS Periscope 13 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom, PDAF, Laser AF, OIS + 48 MP, f/2.2, 17mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S20 Ultra 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + Periscope 48 MP (telephoto), 1/2.0, 0.8µm, PDAF, OIS, 10x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) AF, Super Steady video + 0.3 MP, TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 5 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Realme Narzo 10', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A72', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 M (depth) sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K7', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 8 MP (macro) + B&W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Lite 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1V (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1S (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide/depth sensor) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X2 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '44 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8.3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP, (wide) + 12 MP, (ultrawide) + 2 MP, (macro) + 2 MP, (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO Find X2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 9', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA (Low light sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 10 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto)  PDAF, Laser AF, OIS, 10x hybrid optical zoom + 12 MP (portrait) 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L4', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 9A', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 1.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (Go edition), planned upgrade to Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A92s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro ) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 7 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)+ 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + EMUI 10.1'}
{'device_name': 'Allview V4 Viper Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 5 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A41', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Legacy 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50m 5G', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V19 (Indonesia)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C3 (3 cameras)', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + realme UI 1.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 8A 2020', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S32', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0, planned upgrade to Android 11.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 6', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP B/W (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Realme UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6s (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'LG W10 Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C2s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'LG K61', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 5 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P40 lite E', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) (AOSP + HMS), EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Ace 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A11', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG V60 ThinQ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (standard) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 0.3 MP TOF (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Honor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + Periscope 8 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 (AOSP + HMS) + Magic UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y50', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Unknown selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'TCL 10L', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + TCL UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro) + 2 MP (depth) + 2 MP (dedicated video camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + XOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultra-wide/depth sensor) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Red Magic 3s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Redmagic 2.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0; ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C2 2020', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6 Lite'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 20 lite (China)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP Main camera + 16MP night photography camera + 8MP telephoto camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X50', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP dedicated macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + planned upgrade to Android 10 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) predictive Dual Pixel PDAF, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (telephoto) predictive PDAF, 2x optical zoom, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 12 MP (ultrawide). Additionally, there is a TOF 3D camera.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V20 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MiFavor 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 6S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U20', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 6 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A91 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 12 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X5', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6s (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A51', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee N20', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP+8.0MP+ 8.0MP f/2.0 130° Wide-angle LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP 16.0MP f/2.0 80° Wide-angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 6 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 10s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 28mm (wide) PDAF + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 1v (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5i', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultra-wide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0; ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 855 Racing', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP dual pixel PDAF + 8 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor '}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo 855', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP dual pixel PDAF + 8 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor '}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S95 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 2 MP + 8 MP (depth sensor) + 8 MP (ultrawide angle)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel 3x (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F15', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultra-wide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y9s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee N100', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 10 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A70s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp S7 Android One', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android One (Android 10)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A11x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.0.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Bold N1', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M10', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Flyme 8'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16T', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Flyme 8'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A8', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 2 MP (macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto One Macro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP dual pixel PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'vivo S5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 5 MP depth sensor cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pop 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3WT', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP Camera Sony IMX230'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y3 Standard', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 16 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 4c', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + QVGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3W', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP Camera Sony IMX230'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C6 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot P30', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 20 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pop 2 F', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + HIOS 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A91', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + HIOS 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP+2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7T Pro 5G McLaren', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide), 1/3.1, 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z5i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 4 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (wide) + 16 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (ultrawide) + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG V50S ThinQ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard) Dual Pixel PDAF + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart Pro 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (7P lens) (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto)  2x optical zoom + 5 MP (upscaled to 8MP) (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 12 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Pouvoir 3 Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition) + HIOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y11 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A01', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) AF + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel Y1000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3 V', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), upgradable to Android 10, Android One'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Exodus 1s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) Dual Pixel PDAF, Laser AF, 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No - uses main camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 12', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.5'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Hyper', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Camon 12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.5'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP dedicated macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GX290', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP AF (SONY sensor) + 2 MP dual rear camera with ArcSoftR solution'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP with LED Flash Light'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) PDAF Laser AF OIS + Periscope 13 MP (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 32 MP (telephoto) PDAF, Laser AF, OIS, 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5z', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio Mega 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos V', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP OIS + 13 MP B/W'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS195', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP with LED Flash Light'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 10s Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + MiFavor 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, (wide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '60 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 20 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 6', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'vivo U10', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + Magic UI 3'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y19', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP macro camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) PDAF Laser AF OIS + 32 MP (telephoto) PDAF, Laser AF, OIS, 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo X5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade 20', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS190', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI F2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP primary camera, Samsung GM1, 1/2 image sensor 6-element lens + 13MP ultra wide angle camera, FOV 120° + 5MP depth camera 5MP macro camera, 2cm macro distance'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP 5-element lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Latest Stock Android 10 + System-Wide Dark Theme'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2020', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1, Google Play Services'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A5 (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5s', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S52', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X2', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio Mini', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 Lite (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A71', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide) dedicated macro camera + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + One UI 2'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) omnidirectional + 48 MP (ultrawide) + 8MP telephoto lens + 5MP color filter (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (7P lens) (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto)  2x optical zoom + 5 MP (upscaled to 8MP) (telephoto) 5x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U650S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '108 MP (wide) PDAF, Laser AF + 12 MP (telephoto) Dual Pixel PDAF, Laser AF, 2x optical zoom + 20 MP (ultrawide) Laser AF + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Play (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ZUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9800', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia C1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie (Go edition)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 19s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P8100S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K20 Pro Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10; MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V17', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 3e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9800 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover FieldPro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 30 RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 40 MP (ultrawide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide) + 3D TOF camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + EMUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno3 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + ColorOS 7'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Razr 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + TOF 3D (depth)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) dedicated video camera (1080p) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S68 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony 21 MP + 8 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo V17 (India)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.2'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S40 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto) 3x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide), 1/3.1, 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0 + OxygenOS 10.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K30 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10 + MIUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo NEX 3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Realme XT 730G (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M10s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A9 (2020)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 8', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) + 2 MP, depth sensor + QVGA (Low light sensor) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + XOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A20s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13mm (ultrawide) + 2 MP + 2 MP,  depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab Active Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Fold 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 16 MP (ultrawide) lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP (wide) + 8 MP (wide), depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Pearl K1', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 11 Pro Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide) cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'LG W30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Wildfire X', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, (wide) + 8 MP, (telephoto) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI X', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG W30', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav M6', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo H8 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 13 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'vivo NEX 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 13 MP (telephoto) + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'LG W10', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 11', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + TOF 3D camera'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 13'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y70', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F9', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AL240', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S90 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 12 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 16 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 10.0; OxygenOS 10'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16s Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.7, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF, OIS + 20MP, f/2.6, (telephoto), 1/2.8, 1.0µm, PDAF + 16 MP, f/2.2, 16mm (ultrawide), 1/3.6, 1.0µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9 Meitu Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10.2 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9e', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'LG G8X ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (standard) Dual Pixel PDAF + 13 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/1.9, 26mm (wide), 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q70', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/1.8, (wide), PDAF + 13 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide)+ 5 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); LG UX 7'}
{'device_name': 'LG G8s ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X3 JBL', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (1080p) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5535L Strike Power Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 1/2.55, 1.4µm, dual pixel PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V141', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i18', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6035L Strike Power Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu T20', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF | 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) | 5 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 9X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (depth sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D63', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A90 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Realme XT', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), planned upgrade to Android 10.0 + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'alcatel TCL Plex', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide), 1/2.8, 0.9μm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee X2', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5583 Pay 5.5', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone 2', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF/Laser AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.6, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP depth sensor lenses'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z20', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D62', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, (wide), AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo NH4', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D58', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6.18 in (inches)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A10s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide), AF + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno2 Z', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.7, 26mm (wide), 1/2.0, 0.8µm, PDAF, OIS + 8 MP, f/2.2, 16mm (ultrawide), 1/3.2 + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (wide) predictive Dual Pixel PDAF, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (telephoto), predictive PDAF, 2x optical zoom, 5-axis OIS + 12 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1/4, 1.12µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Action', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.6 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.6 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'E&L D57', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6.18 in (inches)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP A240', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo R6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'E&L 6P', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6.18 in (inches)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9100', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (telephoto), 3x optical zoom, OIS + 16 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP, f/2.0, 0.9µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5084', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9T', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP, f/2.2, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9T Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide) + 8 MP, f/2.4, 53mm (telephoto) + 13 MP, f/2.4, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP, f/2.2, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'E&L 6C', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno A', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Red Magic 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 megapixel + Self-portrait beauty support'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 + Redmagic OS 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N3', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1 A', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'vivo iQOO Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF + 13 MP, f/2.2, (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H30', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 20S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Magic 2.1'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10 Plus 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1.22µm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5584', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo S7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A50s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/2.0, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 5 MP, f/2.2, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), 1.22µm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3a', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP, f/1.8, 28mm (wide), 1/2.55, 1.4µm, dual pixel PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1.12µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G6', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3i', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Honor Play 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 6', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), 1.22µm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A30s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP, f/1.7, PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 5 MP, f/2.2, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 7P', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': '10.or G2', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno2 F', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP B/W + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Phantom 9', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U19e', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), PDAF 20 MP, f/2.6, 52mm (telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); HTC Sense'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5014', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K50S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), PDAF + 5 MP, (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 10 Plus (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 19 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide), PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5i Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF, 8 MP, (ultrawide), 2 MP, f/2.4, 27mm (wide) dedicated macro camera, and 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi CC9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz Elite Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Z1x (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); Funtouch 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G8', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG K40S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 26mm (wide), PDAF + 5 MP, (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga I7 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 µm, AF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5016', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N.A.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N.A.'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry 4', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Magic 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video, Pixel size - 2.0 μm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with Nubia Red Magic 2.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile Revvlry', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 1.12µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.12µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5T', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 28mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF + 16 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide), 1/3.1 + 2 MP, f/2.4, 27mm (wide), dedicated macro camera + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y50', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K10 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ZUI 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia X 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Uses main cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'realme', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4 (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile Revvlry Plus', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.7, 1.22µm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, 1.25µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z51', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 5.0 Lite (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP542', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF / 12 MP, f/2.2, (telephoto), 1.0µm, PDAF, 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0, 0.9µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-1.8-2.4, 27mm (wide) + 12 MP, f/2.1, 52mm (telephoto) + 16 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1.22µm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A6 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus A1s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo Ef9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16th Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, (wide), PDAF + 8 MP, f/2.2, 13mm (ultrawide) + 2 MP, f/2.4 (dedicated macro camera) + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide), PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C16 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M30s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16th', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Maimang 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 8', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6100', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall S10', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE nubia Z18', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/1.6, dual pixel PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); nubia UI 6'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP494', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 13MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP, f/2.0, 26mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'M-Horse M1', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9600', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo NF4 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Main rear camera - 12MP + Secondary rear camera - 20MP + Third rear camera - 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N.A.'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9500 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos X20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos X20', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Gome C7 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gome C7', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Mate 20', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS110', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Pure Android™ 9.0 Pie - Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C7s', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze J5', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Pearl K2', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody P30', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X6 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6i', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (F1.6) + 16MP (F2.2) + 8 MP (F2.4)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP with Aperture F2.0, Face unlock, Sony IMX471 Exmor RS, Mechanical Pop-up Front Camera, Pixel size - 1.0 μm, Digital image stabilization'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen 9.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 X 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '39.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Z557', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Avalon V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP541', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X100', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'itel A46', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live (L2) SD430', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 4s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y80', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Maxvi MS502 Orion', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F27', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart N10', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y12', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live (L2) SD425', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Maxvi MS531 Vega', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 7i', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Y60', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Rock V', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart V10', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Runbo E81', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Maxvi MS401 Sunrise', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'itel A44 Air', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F25', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X27', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E6', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize U3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5528L Strike Forward', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F16', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A60 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3x', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V10 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ark S503 (New)', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Sky', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone P6000 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar S30', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X20', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 7 Pro X625B', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 5.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A1', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony Z15', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1k', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 5.2.1 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar F20', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU G9', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i72', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Z Helio P90', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar C13', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (F1.6) + 16MP (F2.2) + 8 MP (F2.4)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP with Aperture F2.0, Face unlock, Sony IMX471 Exmor RS, Mechanical Pop-up Front Camera, Pixel size - 1.0 μm, Digital image stabilization'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen 9.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony R40', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF, Laser AF + 8 MP, f/2.4, 53mm (telephoto), 1/4, 1.12µm, PDAF, Laser AF, 2x optical zoom + 13 MP, f/2.4, 12mm (ultrawide), 1/3, 1.12µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 20 MP, f/2.2, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo NF4', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia mini 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme X Master Edition', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 5', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A7', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20 Lite 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5500 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Red Magic 3', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C5L', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT R19', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 5i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6 Youth Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi K20', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade L8', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Hummer 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7 Helio P60', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X90', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'TECNO Spark 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + HIOS 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel Y4800', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.1 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Legacy', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 7S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels f/1.8 + 5 Megapixels f/2.2 Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A3 2019', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.5-2.4, 26mm (wide), 1/2.55, 1.4µm, Dual Pixel PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10 MP, f/1.9, 26mm (wide), 1.22µm, Dual Pixel PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'LG Solo LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 8X', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 8.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xolo ZX', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 3 1GB', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 7A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M40', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32-megapixel (f/1.7) + 5-megapixel + 8-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16-megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8S', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld SD200', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X4 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P Smart Z', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3 MT6771', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y15', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee X6', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B260', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16Xs', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z4 Force', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, 27mm (wide), 1/2.9, 1.25µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GS155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld SD100', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP primary camera, Sony IMX398/Samsung S5K2P7, F/1.8, 6P lens + 8 MP ultra-wide angle camera, 120° wide-angle + 5 MP depth camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone 6', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized flip Primary camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie OS with ZENUI 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K13', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Unlock, 0.18 inch Sensor Size, GalaxyCore GC8034 CMOS BSI Sensor, Pixel Size - 1.124 um'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A40s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 17 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video, Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A7H', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 6 ZS630KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 26mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, Laser/PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.4, 11mm (ultrawide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie), ZenUI 6'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i65', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A5', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Legacy Go', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 5G', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U3H', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi kPhone 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A9x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade L130', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Face recognition, CMOS BSI'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with EMUI 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3a XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 Prime 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi kPhone', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'itel A52 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax iOne', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+5MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X6 Xtreme', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 5.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody P20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Z', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); ColorOS 5.2'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K12', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreо Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 62S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (F1.8) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP + 2 MP with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y17', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J7', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP +20MP + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6040L Magic', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP +20MP + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 6E', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 11S', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze K3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize V3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'E&L S618', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot S4', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'E&L S55', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A90 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Vision', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A80', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Flipping main camera module'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Power Plus 5000', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno 10x zoom', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + Periscope 13 MP (telephoto), 5x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + ColorOS 6'}
{'device_name': 'Zen Admire Shine', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI F1 Play', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreо Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z40', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R15', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreо Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP493', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K6 Enjoy', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Hit 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT16S', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G1 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 9 PureView', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels X 5 + TOF (Five Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP with 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Android One'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE N10', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nobby S300', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 7', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5004G Fox', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture,1.12µm sensor,84 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo S1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M13', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A60', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A2 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 4e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.27 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32.33 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nobby A200', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu M8', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S77', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Nobby S500', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X27 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo G8i', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5083 Pay 5', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K12+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'RugGear RG725', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8A Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA A2', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C14 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo EM2', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 800', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P110', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP, f/1.8, 27mm (wide), 1/2, 0.8µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B340', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo E9 Exclusive', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'RugGear RG650', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A16 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 27mm (wide), 1/3, 1.12µm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1/4, 1.12µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo H8', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA G3', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo E9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i 4 2GB', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.6, 26mm (wide), 1/2.6, 1.4µm, predictive Dual Pixel PDAF, 5-axis OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 24mm (wide), 1/4, 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Cyrus CS45', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA A3', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Casper VIA A3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cenava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom H5', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X27', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X90L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i 4', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A40', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Shot', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X25', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Keitai 3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S40', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A20e', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X27 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus E4', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Plus (M2)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C13 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (F2.2) + 16 MP (ultra-wide angle) + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ29', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '31.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio S Max', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody S10', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Conquest S9 MT6757', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP, f/2.0, 0.8µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo iQOO', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide) AF + 5 MP (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'RugGear RG655', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI Power', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP with Face unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo AX5s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody XR', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody P20', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP (ultra-wide angle) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Carl Zeiss Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Sky 3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V15', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32.33 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 9.0 OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A70', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Unlock, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S11', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+5MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P30 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor or 24 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP or 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A3 Lite (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32 GB'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense U30', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '21.27 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'PROTRULY Darling V10S', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Oreo Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16S', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels f/1.8, 1.55 µm + 20 Megapixels 1.0 µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0, 1080P with Face Unlock Feature, AI Powered'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus Z30', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda S60X', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.0, Face Unlock, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Pro (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (16MP + 5MP For 6GB Version)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel (16MP 6GB Version) with Face Recognition, 1.0 um Pixel Size, LED Flashlight,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Pocophone F1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A5s (AX5s)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, AF + 2 MP, f/2.4, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); ColorOS 5.2'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Quest Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 6Z', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense King Kong 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus V7', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda W51', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J5', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Pocophone F2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '64MP main, 8MP ultra-wide and 16MP telephoto cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 10 (Android 10)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A7n', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 5.2.1 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91i India', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/1.8 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 3L', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda W41', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X71', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 8 MP (ultra-wide angle) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Carl Zeiss Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y8C', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense King Kong 5', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 9 Go', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Reno', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP+12MP+5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo); ColorOS 5.2'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda 6A', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A16', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 8 Go', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C13', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Samsung'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Unlock, Interpolated resolution 8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go edition'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 7', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + OxygenOS 9.5.8'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Grace V7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart+ 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP + 16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'NUU Mobile A5L Plus', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P551S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X3 Turbo', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 7', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, AF + QVGA, depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo + Go edition'}
{'device_name': 'Centric S1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K9', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic 2 3D', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Centric G3', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91i MT6762', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Centric G5', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A60', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Centric A2', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5i Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Centric L4', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V10', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '32.33 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Ace2x', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U630S Pop', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview Max 1', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Ace2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 10 Pro 5G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP f/1.7 (primary) + 8MP f/2.4 (telephoto) + 20MP f/2.2 (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG G8 ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G253', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Oxygen 68 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio X8 HD 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo R5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A6 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U620S Pop', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B355', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z4 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Win Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L3', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6 Pro 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + EMUI 9'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Oxygen 63', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Land Rover X', 'manufacturer': 'Lanix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Go', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U620S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia 10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Highscreen Wallet', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Fold', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.51 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Start LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H501S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C1 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GS150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Pass 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Ultimate U570S', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Oxygen 57', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H570S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4001G Cool', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H591S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Zero', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels (Telephoto)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP with Aperture F2.0, Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N20', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'China Mobile A3S', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, OmniVision OV5670 PureCel Sensor, F2.4 Aperture, 5P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AS260', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG V50 ThinQ 5G', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Noa F20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q9 One', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.26 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 3', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ4', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Noa F10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.27 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E401', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.58 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5i Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Mate RS', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91C (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Vue 1', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.58 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Explorer Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5011G Fox View', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10e Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S99i', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E551S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2 V', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 5G Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.51 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G7', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.58 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10e SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 4.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Pure', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5514G Strike Power', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i95', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-601L Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V48', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9700 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-401L Asper', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie); EMUI 9.1'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-style S5501', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 5G SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '10.51 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B7Fox Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V97', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V142', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B7', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'ioutdoor Polar3', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Curve Q454', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 5G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6i Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2 Go Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B6Fox', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Otegaru 01', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo D9', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Argo 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Diamond', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos SH-02L', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GM3+ (3GB)', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A606', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K40', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kogan Agora XS', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Neon', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B6', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 6.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo XRover C', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V128', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B4 mini NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS280', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K50', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y89', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Kogan Agora 8', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Motorized pop-up 32 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + Funtouch 9'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova Lite 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B4 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C6L', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q60', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Kogan Agora 9', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie and Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9 Transparent Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S562Z', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Tribute Empire', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P18K Pop', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F205 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C12', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 TopA10', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S10 SD855', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo U1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A5s', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z92', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Active 1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.96 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A30', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A50', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24.24 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.24 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y85 MT6762', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Active 1', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Vision R2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Joy 1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5010G Spot', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vsmart Joy 1', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5521L Rich Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6010G Practic', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5519L Fast Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A622', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall S5500', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Stone', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Onyx', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Pro (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide) + 10 MP (telephoto) 2x optical zoom + 8 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP (wide) depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo), upgradable to Android 9.0 (Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 Prime 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5514L Strike Power 4G', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Picasso Note', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar C21', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E9', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y16', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A44 Power', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 7R', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (wide) + 5 MP depth sensor or 12 MP (wide) + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 10'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91 (Mediatek)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + Funtouch 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7R', 'manufacturer': 'Ticwatch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xolo Era 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S11', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Fly View', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo One Plus 2019', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Access 50 S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S90', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1X (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X19', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1C (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Prime Q306', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP554', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Android One S5', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Q4151', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun 7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Q357', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun 6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Active 2 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N10', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Blade 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Noa P1', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia X', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Uses main cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Fresh 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5500', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y8', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Primo 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Noa Vivo 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N1', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Life', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreо'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar X1 Notch', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Astra', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V11', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D27', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Rio X', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution - 5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Conquest S12', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Zeon 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93 India', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M30', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo), upgradable to Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y91i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + Funtouch 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M10', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo EF8 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V9', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Yandex Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5302G Velvet 2', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Santin Max 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xolo Era 4X', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V2', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MiGuer M1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V5X', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V3', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'iLA X1', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Santin N1 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V3', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze Y3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody M78 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor, Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with Emotion 9.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V4', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6 Prime 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Santin N1', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E13', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D28', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.02 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y7', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Magic Mars', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with Nubia Red Magic 1.6 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo NEX 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No - uses main camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AL140', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 5C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Fly View Max', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E11', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BL250', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 4 High version', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Aqua', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA X2', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI F1', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E7', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP T155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 4 Standard version', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A509 Jeans', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize YA3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Play', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Power P11', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X60', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Plum Phantom 2', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Power P8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-40', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X80', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda K30', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A7', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 8', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GL355', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Max 1', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony E90', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-4', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis N1-550 Cruiser', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C1 Shine', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda K10', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS80', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 1/3.1, 1.12µm, PDAF + 5 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo), upgradable to Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G355', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C2', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme U1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-3', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP402', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome Fenmmy Note', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B245', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Stock Android 9 Pie + Luxury Ceramic Design'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C1', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-2', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel S10', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Ukozi Uone', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A511 Harmony', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Infinity 12', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Top', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze H5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Play', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad M3', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A3', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Z455', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia M3', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Infinity 11', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ginzzu RS8502', 'manufacturer': 'Great Wall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-1', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'itel P13 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y Max', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + EMUI 8.2'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U25 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Jet', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'itel A15', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Luck NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier I8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Benefit M9', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Ace', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'itel A14', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B450', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5 Pro GT', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Z250', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo X5', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Wizard 2', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar E1 Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5 Pro GT', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5s', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu V7', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze U3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MiGuer M1', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom R17', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo AX7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A512 Harmony Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V5', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Goophone Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1X Evolve', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V12', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BL150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Vira', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5015L First', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 12s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Uniwa F4000', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vargo VX3', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Sunset NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6T McLaren Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen 9.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody S9', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cricket Wireless Wave', 'manufacturer': 'CMCC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 55S Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG X5 Android One', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.26 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Cricket Wireless Vision', 'manufacturer': 'CMCC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Aero', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V94', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Flash', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A6', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 7S', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E500S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Spark Go', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z81', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze V3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Pluto', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Toughbook P-01K', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Max 2s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS60Z', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E500', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y95', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 Lite 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition) + EMUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Illumina', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI One Max', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS40G', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS50G', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'iLA R1', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P85 NXT', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'GuoPhone X3', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y73', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS50X', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark Helo 256GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 10MP + 8MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot A5', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A5', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C10', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '3.15 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X23 Symphony Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P60', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Rosso', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5710 Infinity X1', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide), AF + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Haier P10', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera DuraForce Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9600 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Stock Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R2 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.57 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 11', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic 2 256GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R17 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q9', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U2', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze G5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A23', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5014 Evo M4', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 6', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Pro (M2)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Aura', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max (M2)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y73 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Quest', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Z1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Red Magic 2 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Y27', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 512GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Red Magic 2', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T8', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S10', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel IdeaXTRA', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5s', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu C9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Symbol X', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5 Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Feel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C8', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + Funtouch 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z9', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu C9', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Zeon 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Slimline', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A9', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 6X', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis N1-570 Space', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H12 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A510 Jeans', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5i', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung W2019', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel PowerPro P41', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5X Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U9', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V155', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U9 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Advance 5.2 HD', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL 2', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark Helo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP A150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Exodus 1', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn K9 Smart Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX 3 Palace Museum Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP + 2 MP with Aperture F2.0, Popp-up Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo) MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel LX', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview A10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max (M1) ZB556KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Polaroid Cosmo C6', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 5 Infinity Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Lite (L1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview A10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5002G Fun', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Advance A6 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Polaroid Cosmo K2', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Xpression Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Infie 77', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5520L Silk', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense King Kong 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 4 Diwali Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo Go', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y81i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1 Plus 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense King Kong 4', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS650', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy Max 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 7P', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS550', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Grand M2 2018 16GB', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone PX', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Photo Pro', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6s 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J4 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X11', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X7 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X10S', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U23', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5 Style', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4608 x 3456 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade View Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z1 Youth Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Joy 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S80 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga X1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8C 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3 V1813BA', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 44', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga X1', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6016L Mercury', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ54', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Selfie Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense 2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'EL K20', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X7', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG it V36', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V145', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + EMUI 8.2'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ53', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Zero', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.6 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Indigo', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V98', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S209', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Compact 4G', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 11', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 530', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5517L Twin Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 5 Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad E2C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense A6', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.1 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, Portrait Mode'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP571', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi iPro', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Razer Phone 2', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X2 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C11', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo S9', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Platinum P9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M3', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 22', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu X8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy Max', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Tetra', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP1', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C1', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K1 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Platinum P9 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8x', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Screen Fingerprint Edition 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S17', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 11', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3T', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with, Face Recognition, f/2.2 Aperture, Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Orbit', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx X1 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Advance L4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Screen Fingerprint Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M11', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Alfa 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu V8 Standard version', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Power 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition, 3P lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Pay 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu V8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Rebel 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7 3GB', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6200L Aurora', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot King Kong 3', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 600', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5300G Velvet View', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Vox V40 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7 Deluxe', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze F5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 (2019) 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + EMUI 8.2'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Style', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon iAir2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Base 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9 Plus 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Lite 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.9, 1.4μm + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S80', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ37', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA3', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.87 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.9, 1.4μm + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 8GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 10MP + 8MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Experience 9.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i2x', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'AGM H1', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A3', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Z18s', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2,0 Aperture, 1.12 um pixel size, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Nubia UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 10MP + 8MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Experience 9.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5710', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 13MP, Secondary front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide), AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 6', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 6 Pro 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio Mega 2018', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11 SD660', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H12', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Konka D9', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Pass Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4501G Fox Easy', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone Xs Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.16 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max SD660', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5000G Velvet Easy', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S48c', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Z355', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Click2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone Xs', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.16 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M10', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Grand M2 2018', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone Xr', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3, 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.2 MP (f/2.4, 31mm), 720p@30fps, face detection, HDR, FaceTime over Wi-Fi or Cellular'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9600 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with f/2.2 Aperture, Wide-Angle Lens - 80.4 degree'}, 'operating_system': 'Stock Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze E5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with, Face Recognition, f/2.2 Aperture, Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx X1 Pro 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 5S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 5MP with Interpolated to 13MP, Face Recognition, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov V31', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Access 57', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': '360 N7 Pro', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16X', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos D10', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji Z33', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A4', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Grace P7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y55', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R17', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': '360 N7 Lite', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi PocoPhone F1 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ioutdoor X', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y50', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi PocoPhone F1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max SD636 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7C AUM-L41', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotions 8.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y10', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T8s', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P490', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X23', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max SD636', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y30', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 2S', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels (f/1.8 Aperture) + 5 Megapixels (f/2.0 Aperture)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan 6.6.5'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei 8x', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C2', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with LG UX'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F9 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Candy', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Yota Devices YotaPhone 3', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 Note 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo AX5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Power Plus 3', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG V40 ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'YU Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Yu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live (L1) Go Edition', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z60s', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 4.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U12 Life', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo S6 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS100', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Andy 4E5 8GB', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z91E', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 4.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Epic T', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U17', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion XL150 Abakan', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S3X', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 Lite (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Konka D8', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'itel A45', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V9 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Andy 5E5', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao E-Sport', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 7C 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'itel A22 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P8', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Key2 LE 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo H7s', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress City', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A22', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GM3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Key2 LE', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 7C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'NUU Mobile G2', 'manufacturer': 'NUU Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y83 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Yota Devices Yota 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7 Plus ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A62', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Y', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Atom 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P4 Quad', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y97', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P10', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XI Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S55 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A7x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AS160', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel M5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7 Fit', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9 with 80 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with LG UX'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP2', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI Z2 Special Edition', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q8 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7 One', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9 with 80 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Maimang 7', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz 4E7', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Visual UI (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D6', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris C', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze E7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL5500 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GH7i', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y81s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X3', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Click NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F8s', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i120', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4608 x 3456 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Forest', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X1i', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i15', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5516L Twin', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji Z11', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Power 2', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XI', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony G100', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2 Go', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Harry 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Lions 6', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Funk', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 7', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Sky 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.4 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.6 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.4 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Reef', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'E&L K20', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A30', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp C10', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9N 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp B10', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Optim', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S506m', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X2i', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S1', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution - 5 MP, F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.87 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6800 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9N', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H18', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 10 256GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z61 2GB', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG Harmony 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5056 Fresh', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Hercls L925', 'manufacturer': 'Hasee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Grand Prime Plus 2018 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao Imagine 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U7 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Vega', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 7', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U7', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S70 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X70', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z61', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Grand Prime Plus 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.2 + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (EMUI 8.2) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee K10 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Recognition. ArcSoft'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note9 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 5', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit A150', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note9 SD845', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 5V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K8', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 10 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall S1', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP + 2 MP Megapixels with 1.2 um Pixel Size, Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'THL T9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with SW 8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z1i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI One', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture, Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P11', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 5', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 10 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Win', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K11 Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V135', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI One Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture, Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Blade', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee K10', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Recognition. ArcSoft'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar S20', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylo Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Sol 3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao Note5x', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone Soldier', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel Sony IMX220'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes 16 Megapixel with Aperture f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Eclipse', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Play Android Oreo (Go Edition)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y15 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, OmniVision OV5675 PureCel Sensor, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 NougatAndroid 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y15 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 15', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao R15', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Pocket 18×9', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Power 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 9', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GL255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio G4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 24 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun 18×9', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom H10', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos X9', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Mega', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Spice F311', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 12', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry EvolveX', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Prime 18×9 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G250', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji Z9', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.42 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5512L Strike Forward', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5702 Spring', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture, 1.0 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Evolve', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Spice K601', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Prime 18×9 3G', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart+ (Plus)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 2 Megapixels with Digital zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5515L Fast', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio X1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S70', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C9', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee T3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5077', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 3i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 2 Megapixels with Digital zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Emotion 8.2 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 3 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z61', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F205', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5076', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar X1 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y71i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Twin', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi i2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C9A', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5075', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Kantan Sumaho', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze G7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C7A', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Champ', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos P1', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On8 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On6', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.78 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Infie 33', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'PLUZZ PL4010 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doov A55', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5081', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9500', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 V 2nd Gen', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 V 3th Gen', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Infie 3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Supra Smartphone Full Specification', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, 1.12 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'PLUZZ PL5510 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Energy 18×9', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno F2 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Game', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yes'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee F2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U3 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Jean', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP552', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Joy Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP517', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wieppo E1', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V96', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P612', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Gome C71', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 2.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO GOLF2', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Ares', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture, 85 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gome S1', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 1.5 (Android 6.1 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Cruise', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji S12', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P521', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, f/2.4 Aperture, Face Recognition, Interpolated resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with ROG Gaming X Mode UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with MIUI V9'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H500S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO GOLF1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Pear', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C6', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee F2', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 8.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO HOT1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Selfie Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GF7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P9000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO Mini1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'None'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6015L Universe', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Click', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylusα', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO G1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V92', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 2 Plus (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Refine', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/1.9 with Samsung ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL4015', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5-Megapixel Main Auto Focus With Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2170', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixel Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Achieve', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Note (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL4010', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pouvoir 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit W289', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.29 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+24MP with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24MP Front Camera with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4077 Shark Mini', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile Blue 5', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO G4', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + O.3 MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Amp Prime 3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel G9', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition, Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Trix 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel OK6000 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 2 Go Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U7 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel S11', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Fire', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gome S7', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO G3', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Wolf', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Pad 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android x.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel S9', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry KEY2', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, 1.120 µm Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P90', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, F2.2 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo NEX S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gome Fenmmy Note', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Allview A9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo NEX', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5111L Bliss', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 6', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition,1.120 µm Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP f/2.0 + 16 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6T', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5707 Next', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress New', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Frost', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld K1', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Phonic', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo R5', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions T1 Lite VR', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Click', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OKWU Pi Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OKWU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7P', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion B145', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7C Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Disco', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4160 x 3120 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S6 Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi V5', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V150', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Grand M3', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S509', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GM3', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S6', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylus Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S12', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Dido OS 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee F1', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Dido OS 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Spring', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Play', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.2 + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (EMUI 8.2) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S55', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi i2', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'EL W45', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp X4', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P515', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels with 2.0um Pixel Size, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Wide 3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 6A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo), planned upgrade to Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Explorer Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P520', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo RX6', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit C155', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X50L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ3', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i75', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V140', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8e Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS370 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 8MP f/2.0 with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.4 Front Camera with LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5510', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Visual UI (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M8C', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V44', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5010', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS370', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 8MP f/2.0 with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.4 Front Camera with LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion B140', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A73s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS180', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Bear', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3 High Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Smile UX (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y81', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'EL W40', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS185', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS180', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8Q', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F7 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with MIUI V9'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5206L Balance', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio X1 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q7', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio S1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q7 Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C2', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Qingyou XT1799', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio S1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S Light Luxury', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.7, 1.12µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/1.7 Aperture, 1.22µm & Auto focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Comio P1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pouvoir 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X5 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '3.15 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG X2 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5800', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar XQ Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Premier Pro LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 NOugat'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar CQ', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit A250', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.36 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5001L Contact', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit N151', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.09 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Play', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Play 7', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone X', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture, LED Flash, Face Recognition, Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P513', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V120', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P5130', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo Selfie 1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P212', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.08-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Doov C70', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T9', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J6', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze D5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y3 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee V2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash, F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9500 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels Sony IMX298 + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Samsung 3L8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2140', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': '360 N7', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor T1', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP HD'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Swift 4G S626L', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor S950', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'No rear-mounted camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Included'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV 5800', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 2 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium X588', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.31 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL9000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5211 Strike', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P211', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.08-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium S386', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor T2 Walkie-Talkie Phone', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.57 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor X', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+8MP, F/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S327', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S99', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Sony Exmor RS CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Konka S5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 6.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Junior Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P101', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium V787+', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld VK7000', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C4', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP514', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z3 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-5412 max', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize Q3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 2', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P95', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-501 Club', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Sleek Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Grace B7', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP401', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga I7', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Evolveo StrongPhone G8', 'manufacturer': 'Evolveo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K30', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ14', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 3 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium X596', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 Prime 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Emotion 8.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M15', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ52', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Evolveo StrongPhone G2', 'manufacturer': 'Evolveo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 3', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Compact', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Magnum X1', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live L1', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze X5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ51', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium X598', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel f/2.0 + 5 Megapixel with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ26', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5800 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Storm', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2170', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry KEY2', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.29 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S318', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P1510', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart C551 Ultra Power 6200', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio View', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 10', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S395', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y75s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart C502 Ultra Power 5000', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Digno J', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Active', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'SIRIN LABS FINNEY Blockchain', 'manufacturer': 'SIRIN LABS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (SIRIN OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S257', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo Hot1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J3', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with AF and Single-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2160', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X6', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart A554 Slim Power 3800', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/1.8 + 20 Megapixels Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi S2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12-Megapixel + 5-Megapixel With PDAF Phase Focus F/2.2 Iris Lens LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16-Megapixel With AI Portrait Mode, Front Single Photo False'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi S2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 + 5 Megapixels f/2.0 (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Nova', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with AF and Single-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris X2', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Benefit S505', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions T1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doov C10', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5701L Slim', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion Z150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5008L Brave', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 7', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut R1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP + 20MP Dual Camera with dual high display flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS based on AndroidTM depth customization'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao GM-T21', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld Mix3', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity F17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lanix Ilium Alpha 950 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Lanix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao GM-T11', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6001L Jumbo', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart A504 Slim Power 3200', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Devil', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor, 3 element lens, Wide angle lens 76.9°, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K7', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Power', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.16 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lanix Ilium Alpha 950', 'manufacturer': 'Lanix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile LT100', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 8', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 720P'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao GM-T51', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Sky', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart A404 Slim Power 1800', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BLU R1 HD', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao T55', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Risio 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG V35 ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Play MSM8917', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool2', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 4A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart C571 Fingerprint', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI Z2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Play MSM8920', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C5S', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Realme 1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus Vision 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y83', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony Roar V150', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp A2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 2 Special Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '11.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Pro (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (16MP + 5MP For 6GB Version)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel (16MP 6GB Version) with Face Recognition, 1.0 um Pixel Size, LED Flashlight,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Konka T1', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash , CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 6.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y53i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 3.0 OS (Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Kult Ambition', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar Zumbo Power', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Energy', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K11', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Kult Impulse', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5209L Strike LTE', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Pass', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7A Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z18 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 5MP with CMOS sensor, 0.1 seconds focusing speed, F1.7 aperture, and NeoVision 7.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with AI beauty pre-filling light, F2.0 aperture, and 1.12um large pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1.0'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6000L Aurora', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C3', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N7', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels Sony Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos C7', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5500L Advance', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sonim XP8', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee K3', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview V3 Viper', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z18 mini', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2,0 Aperture, 1.12 um pixel size, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Nubia UI'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos C5A', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 6X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20-Megapixel AI dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20-Megapixel Healing self-timer'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2 SE', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera) 1.25 micron Pixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels, 1.029 um pixel size, Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 6P', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ5003L Shark Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TCL Y660', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos N1', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 86 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee Apex', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx B510 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao K1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'FreeMe OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 5', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21MP+5MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 5MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4585 Fox View', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao T8+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow (Yun OS 5.1)'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P9 Life', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx A453 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P100', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Duo', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-502 Shot', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Nero', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-503 Target', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.4 + 0.3 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Hit Q401 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '640 x 480 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Elf S8', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris VS', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 4P Lens 0.98 µm/pixel Pixel Size, Samsung S5K4H8 CMOS BSI Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'NUU Mobile G3', 'manufacturer': 'NUU Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with Face Recognition, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 550', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F8', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Freetel Priori 5', 'manufacturer': 'Freetel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Plum Compass 2', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pouvoir 1', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Tiger', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-5434 Club', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Freetel Rei 2 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Freetel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile S15', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris VS Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 4P Lens 0.98 µm/pixel Pixel Size, Samsung S5K4H8 CMOS BSI Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP551', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Titan 2', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile X36', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'OS: Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G2', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Eagle 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit T189', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.8, 1.25 µm) + 20 MP (f/1.8, 1.0 µm), 2x optical zoom, dual pixel phase detection autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, (f/2.2, 1.0 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5012L Rich', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G6', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED Flash, 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP510', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Active', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1920 x 1080 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G5', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad A1', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Orion s5204', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 5MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP + 2MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Haier G51', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture, Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 4A', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP550', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 8', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Basio 3', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar S11', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels with Face Recognition, 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens #2 Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Sugar OS 3.3 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Haier L8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5009L Trend', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels Sony IMX486 (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Aperture f/2.0, Sony IMX376 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Android One) OS with MIUI 9.5'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Apollo s5036', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP455', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Qua Phone QZ', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5591 Jeans', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Uday', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo EF7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony P9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Apollo Quattro s5037', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+2MP with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP453', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5005L Intense', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 1.65um Pixel Size, LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier G8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ2 Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Digno A', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V130', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels F/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 Samsung with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo S3', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5594 Strike Power Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'KEECOO P11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Keecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A20', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera DuraForce Pro KC-S702', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao Momo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony P11', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Samsung'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S61', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo (Upgraded to Android P)'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Start', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5508L Next LTE', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Small Fresh 5s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 Megapixel With Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL3', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Celkon UniQ', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE A530', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Joy', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i110', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C6', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5007L Iron', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5730 Infinity', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (SW 13MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 55S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Royale Quattro s5702', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+2MP with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony Roar V78', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 Samsung'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Celkon CliQ 2', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee K1 Trio', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 60S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5507L Iron Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xtouch X10', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Saphir 50X', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GH7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i6030 Note X', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (Samsung Sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i70', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion ML245 Electron', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee Rainbow', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5340 Choice', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doov A15s', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee K5', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ34', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2 with 720P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F7s', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5071 Iron-X1', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion ML450 Super Force', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel (Interpolated 13MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i100', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Samsung f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov A19', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'M-Horse Pure 2', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (13MP Interpolated)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Skin Buffring, Face Lift, Big Eyes, SLR (8MP Interpolated)'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo HM4+', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A506 Crystal', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov V15', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 3.2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5001 Evo M3', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion G150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov V33', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion Z255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5012 Evo M2', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A552 Joy Max', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5581', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Andy 5E4', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'M-Horse Pure 3', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos Y5s', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A505 Joy Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU A5 Energy', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5032 Evo X2', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion Z155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5532 Space X2', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion X150 Metal', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut 3', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan 4.x (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 16MP with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Q3001', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android, v6 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.7 + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Auto HDR, Gyro EIS, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 5P Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 3.2 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT70', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.8 + 5 MP with the Single-LED flashlight and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel f/2.8 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C9', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P2', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.7 + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0 with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (ColorOS 5.0) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel f/1.7 + 20 Megapixel f/1.7 + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo (EMUI 8.0) OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K9', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S8', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 5.0MP Sony with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max (M1) S425', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.0 + 8 MP Dual Back cameras with LED Flash, Gyro EIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP f/2.2 Front cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon X', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash, CMOS Sensor, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 3e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 16+2 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion 8.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Power 5', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP+5MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HOMTOM S9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0, 1080p & Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.8 + 5 Megapixels f/2.4 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13+2 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Detection'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI 8.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash, CMOS Sensor, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max (M1) S430', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 + 8 Megapixel with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 5MP f/2.0 with LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP Dual Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE ZFive G LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT20', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow (Color OS )'}
{'device_name': 'iLa Silk', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13+2 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 5P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo One Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.6MP+13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS v8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S60 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Samsung S5K4H8YX CMOS Sensor, F2.8 Aperture, 87 Degree Wide Angle Lens, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT16 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels with Hybrid Zoom, LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Titanium Jumbo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee X1', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Front camera with 1080P Video Recording'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax X507', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP Primary Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT16', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED Flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 1600 x 1200 Pixels Image Resolutions'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow Operating System'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Detection, f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot P20', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Verso', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 megapixels with LED, Digital image stabilization, Touch to focus, Face detection, Digital zoom, Geo tagging'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Itel it5250', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Not Available'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X3', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT3', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H590S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Single-LED Flash and AF 16MP + 0.3MP Dual Back cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 03MP Dual Front cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9+ SD845', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F1.7 Aperture, Laser autofocus, PDAF Focus, Dual Video Call, Auto HDR, Pixel Size 1.22µm, Sensor 1/3.6-inch'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark CM', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Quad-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with DualTone LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia N3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+5MP rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P490S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 0.3MP with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP + 0.3MP Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 2 MP, phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat Go', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5 ZE620KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 Megapixels with OmniVision OV8856 PureCel Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 83 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M7', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (SW 16MP) + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Moto E5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5z ZS620KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 Megapixels with OmniVision OV8856 PureCel Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 83 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Lite Snapdragon 430', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.2 + Unknown Megapixel (12mm) wide angle with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel + 20 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U19', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X50', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel + 0.3 Megapixel f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '18 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 Pro 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Plus (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 8MP f/2.0 with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels withBeauty Mode, f/2.0 Aperture, 85 ° Wide Angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with ZenUI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15 Dream Mirror Edition', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 4.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP5000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nogat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P4', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Z3 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.6) + 8 MP, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.0, 1.4 µm), dual-LED dual-tone flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S16', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Teclast A10S', 'manufacturer': 'Teclast', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP (f/2.0) + 8 MP (17mm, no AF), gyro EIS, phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 25mm), gyro EIS'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.6) + 8 MP,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.0, 1.4 µm), dual-LED dual-tone flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia V18', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A83 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8-megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S7', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT26', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5z (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.8, 24 mm, 1.4 µm) + Unknown MP (12mm), phase detection autofocus, gyro EIS, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 24mm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z91', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'UMI OS (Android 8.1 Oreo) OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S12', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung W2018', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP Primary Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y85 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu S6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21 UD', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.8 + 5 Megapixel f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.0 with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 12 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT30', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor View 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '(16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 20 Megapixel) with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 40 MP (f/1.8, 1/1.7, OIS) + 20 MP (f/1.6) + 8 MP (f/2.4), Leica optics, 3x optical zoom, phase detection and laser autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, autofocus, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel (SW 8MP) Sony Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Apex', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 4', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT27', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P16K Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Max', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P10000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel primary camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5-megapixel front shooter for selfies'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG X4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8110 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No Primary Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'KaiOS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max 490S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8-megapixel primary camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5-megapixel front shooter for selfies'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Infinity Life', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3, 1.12 µm), autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat), planned upgrade to Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z50', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Go', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDigi A1', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13M+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS v8.1 Oreo (Stock Android)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U12+ (Plus)', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.6 + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels f/2.0, HDR Support'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn A9 Indian', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Camera 5 MP Primary Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo XRover', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 0.18 inch Sensor Size, 1.103um Pixel Size, Sony IMX219PQ Exmor R CMOS BSI Sensor,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Lite S630', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 20 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Sony Imx376 Exmor RS sensorLED Flashlight'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Roar 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel AF and Single-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Zone 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 100 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 AI', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.9 +5 MP f/2.0, 1.4 μm with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Sony Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 12', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT37', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ2 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with 1080P, Gyro EIS'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee V2', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels, Face Recognition,LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0, 1.12 µm with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ2', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels f/2.0, 1.22 µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3X', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0, + 5 Megapixel f/2.2 with Dual-Tone LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT17', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 1600 x 1200 Pixels Image Resolutions'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X4 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP +8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 & Pixel size 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30S ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition, 1.12 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT37 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30S+ ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition, 1.12 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels 1/2.9, 1.25 µm + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Powered Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG X300', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT50', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Power 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Tempo Go', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V9 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8 Sirocco', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel + 13 Megapixel f/1.7 with AF and Dual LED Flash Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Samsung BSI CMOS Sensor, PDAF, 1.4um, f/2.0, 78.4˚, Phase Detection, Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.5-2.4 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Plus Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP + 12MP f/1.5-2.4 with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 720P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10+ (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP or 8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On Max', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash, F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 2 American Version', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Leadership 8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Single LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Eclipse', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera f/2.0, 1.4 µm with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A85', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 5P Lens, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 3.2 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4 Plus (USA)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.2 Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10α (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C7 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Nxt', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos EA', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX 2 Special Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Omnivision OV5675 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X4 (6GB)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP +8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 & Pixel size 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T1 Premium Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (S5K3P3 Sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (Interpolated to 13.0MP) f/2.0 aperture with Selfie Softlight'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A5 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.8 with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Hawkeye', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5T International Version', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 1.0µm pixel, EIS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen OS Powered (Android 7.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5A Global', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, PDAF Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 (2018) USA', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera) f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with LED Flash, Face Beauty'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Tiger X', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Active', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, F1.7 Aperture, Dual Video Call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 MP (Dual Camera) LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 720p Video Recoding, Moonlight LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Jasper LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Priv', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '18 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6 International Version', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture,1.12µm sensor,84 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Folder 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5A Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, OmniVision PureCel Sensor, PDAF Focus, 76,4 ° Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K6 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDigi Z Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3L8 Sensor, 6P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 720p Video Recoding, Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 8 MSM8998', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 + 12 Megapixels OIS, 1.55µm pixel size'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F1.7 Aperture,Smart Autofocus,1/3.6-inch Sensor Size,Selective Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI C Note', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with GalaxyCore GC5005 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z6E', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V870', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Aperture f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 8 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 + 12 Megapixels OIS, 1.55µm pixel size'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F1.7 Aperture,Smart Autofocus,1/3.6-inch Sensor Size,Selective Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Android One X1', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.4 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F1.9 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A520', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 (China version)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Pixel Size 1.25μm, PDAF Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI G', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia M2 Play', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Chuwi HiBook Pro Z8350', 'manufacturer': 'Chuwi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Rear camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10, Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDigi Z', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3L8 Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Starmobile Up Groove', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Chuwi SurBook', 'manufacturer': 'Chuwi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10 OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 (64GB)', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Pro 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 720p Video Recording, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 3.6 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Lenny 4', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos L2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.1 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 85 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A521', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI Z1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 5 Megapixels Samsung S5K3L8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI C Note 2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels, SAMSUNG S5K3L8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels GC5005'}, 'operating_system': 'UMI OS Powered Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C5', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld Mix', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6 B20', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture,1.12µm sensor,84 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Pro 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 720p Video Recording, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 3.7 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI S', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels +5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Beauty Mode Selfie'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A612', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M E2', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Quad-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow with Flyme 6.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel 10000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE N939Sc (Blade A711)', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel 10000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI C2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels, Samsung S5K3L8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels GC5005'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with PDAF, 1.12um, f/2.0, 78.4˚, Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Spark', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Note 5.5', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo X', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with PDAF Focus, 0.1s Focus, Samsung S5K5E2 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'XOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia N1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 720p Video Recording, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 3.7 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI Crystal Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S2 Higher Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS sensor, 1.4µm large pixel, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions T1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI Crystal MT6737T', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera) Samsung Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (SW 16.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (SW 16.0MP) with 1.019 um Pixel Size, ON Semiconductor AR1335 CMOS Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor E', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 13 Megapixels Front Facing Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia M2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia N2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 2um Pixel Size, Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S2 Standard Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS sensor, 1.4µm large pixel, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U22', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13.0MP) + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (SW 8.0MP) + 2 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'UMI OS (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Mars Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (Real 8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (Real 2.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone GQ3028', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, OmniVision OV5648 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F1.8 Aperture, 80.7 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Phase Detection'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Avid 916', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 Lollipop OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp R1', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia M2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 2um Pixel Size, Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 V', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with TouchWiz UI'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Gemini', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 5 Megapixels Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow Upgradable to Android 7.0 Naught'}
{'device_name': 'LG Rebel 3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Aperture F2.0, 5P Lens,1080p Video Recording, Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4 Plus MT6737', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 5-element lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Tiger Lite 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Perx', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A602', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 G9500', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4 MT6737', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S8', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Amp Prime 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Prestige 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 6 Global', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with UltraPixel Camera, Sony IMX268 Sensor, Magic Mirror mode, Face Beauty 3.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z2 Force', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Dual LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 G950F', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5X Global Version', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels +12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Magic Mirror,1080p video,Face Beauty 3.0,Real Time Beauty'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Mini Standard Edition', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels+13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, 5P Lens, F2,0 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A1 (5X)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash & 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat Upgrade to Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955U', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Zmax Champ LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Sol 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp S3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense Basic', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Wide 2 J727S', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955F', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE ZFive L LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 5 MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp R1S', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Max 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2,2 Aperture, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 G950K', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note Fan Edition MSM8996', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Samsung S5K4E6 ISOCELL Sensor, 22mm Wide,Dual Video Call,Auto HDR,F1.7 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 5 MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP F/2.0 Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Zmax Grand LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note Fan Edition Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Samsung S5K4E6 ISOCELL Sensor, 22mm Wide,Dual Video Call,Auto HDR,F1.7 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955K', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Pi', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X5', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 8 MP f/1.8 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo, Android One OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 7s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2,2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F1.9 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955FD', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Max XL', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, CMOS Sensor,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Halo', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 (2017) J330', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu E3', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C10 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/1.8 with Dual LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Pro (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A7 2018 (Rumored)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LeTV LeEco Le Pro 3 Elite X722', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, 1.4μm Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U18', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13.0MP) with 1.127 um Pixel Size, OmniVision OV8856 PureCel CMOS Sensor, 0.18 inch Sensor Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Exalt LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'Proprietary OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lava X28 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U12', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20MP + 20MP f/1.7, phase detection autofocus, OIS, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 3.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 100 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Mega 2 Plus Q426+', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z25', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 3.3 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Galaxycore gc5025 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-camera setup on the back (a standard and a wide-angle lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No Data Available'}, 'operating_system': 'Android, v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Spark Vdeo Q415', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40MP Tri Cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android (8.0)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Q354', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE 2', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 7', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M6', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Charge', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans I8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iNew U7 4G', 'manufacturer': 'iNew', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Evok Note E453', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, F2.2 Aperture, 1.4 micron pixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 3.3 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 2s', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 + 12 MP | f/1.8, 1/2.55 + 1.4 µm f/2.4, 1/2.9, 1.0 µm | dual pixel dual phase detection autofocus, 4-axis OIS, 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Evok Power', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Lenny 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld VK7000', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Supreme 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q6α', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Note 2', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld T2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'THL Knight 1', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with Interpolated Resolution Up to 13 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.6, 26mm, 1/2.55, 1.4 µm, Dual Pixel PDAF) + 12MP (f/2.4, 52mm, 1/3.6, 1 µm, AF), OIS, phase detection autofocus, 2x optical zoom, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.6, autofocus, 1440p, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Magnus HD Q421', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Robby 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP (f/2.0, 1.12 µm), phase detection & laser autofocus, Carl Zeiss optics, OIS, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 5 MP (f/2.0, AF, 1080p) + 5 MP (f/2.4, no AF)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Pace Q402', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Spice V801', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q6+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon CM', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans A6', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn A40 Indian', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Yunique 2', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iLA D1 Big Eyes', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon I', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, LED Flash, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Evok Dual Note', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 +5 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with AF and LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia M2 Lite (NX573J)', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'YU Yureka Black', 'manufacturer': 'Yu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 84.3 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno W3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn K9 Smart Eco', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'YU Yureka 2', 'manufacturer': 'Yu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'iLA S1 King Kong', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T8', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Sony IMX362 Exmor RS CMOS Sensor, Aperture F1.8, 6P Lens, 1.44 um Pixel Size, 1080p Video, Milbeaut Image Processor (Fujitsu), OIS,'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 3.5 OS (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans S3', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4 Pro Windows Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1080p Video, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu M8', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels SONY IMX362 Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with SamSung 2L7 Sensor, 1080p Video,'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 3.5 OS (Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS)'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Titanium Frames S7', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iLA X', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Maze Blade', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 84° Wide Angle Lens, 1.4 µm Pixel Size, Sony IMX 179 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS MX', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T8s', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels Sony IMX230 Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Sony IMX362 Exmor RS CMOS Sensor, Aperture f/1.8, 6P Lens, 1.44 um Pixel Size + 5 Megapixel SAMSUNG 4E8'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.0 OS (Android 7.1 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U3', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus M5s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8V (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG LS7 4G LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel IdealXCITE', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu M8s', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels SONY IMX362 Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+5MP with Phase Detection, 6P Lens, OIS, SONY IMX230 Exmor RS CMOS Sensor, Aperture f/1.8, 1080p Video,'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.0 OS (Android 7.1 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MAZE Comet', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu V6', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+12MP Dual Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A50', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X400', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel XL2', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.3 Megapixels 1.55µm, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/1.8, 1.4 µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Maze Alpha X', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Sony IMX258'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0, Sony IMX219'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Fiesta 2 CDMA', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LYF Water 7S', 'manufacturer': 'LYF', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Green Pomelo', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 & Pixel size 1.0µm & LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A30 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LYF C459', 'manufacturer': 'LYF', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Camera with Yes, Red Eye Reduction, Smile Detection, Panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP Camera selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A30 Fierce', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus A1', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Fortune', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20 V', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 Power', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U50', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat, OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Signature Edition', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide, 1.12um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LYF C451', 'manufacturer': 'LYF', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Primary Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo P1', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, 3P Lens, 77.9 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 Lite (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 Novo', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X53', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Cameras) (RGB + Monochrome)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 85 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Pro Mode, 1.4µm Pixels, OV5695 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Risio 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 5 Cricket', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with High CRI LED Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X55', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo P1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels +2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 3P Lens, 77.9 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 Lite (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 7 High Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lava X41 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Grace LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel CameoX', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Tribute Dynasty', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K4 Novo', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'MEIZU MA5', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus M7s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iNew L7', 'manufacturer': 'iNew', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Lenny 3 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X500', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z90', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 8 MP + 2 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T5c', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels 3P Lens, 1.12um*1.12um'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'iNew I9', 'manufacturer': 'iNew', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2` Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Nougat Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko U Pulse', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5T Star Wars Limited Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 1.0µm pixel, EIS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen OS Powered (Android 7.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Fiesta LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Rebel 2 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu A5', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Camera Set UP (One Front + One Back)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus A2', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z6', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 2.813um Pixel Size, GalaxyCore GC0409 Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Hali', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z7', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko U Pulse Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A71 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 1.4um Pixel Size, Face Recognition, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T5s', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Sony Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with AF and LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.0 Powered Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 1.12 micrometer, Auto Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 2.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense E76 Infinity Elegance', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu E2 Transformers Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Exposure compensation, 1.4 µm pixel, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow with Flyme 6.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F26', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1.4um Pixel Size, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 2.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot S3', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Wim', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash, 1080p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Wim Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash, 1080p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 3', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova Lite 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI 8.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 4', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1.4um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 2.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans K5000', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with CMOS Sensr, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 3.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R11', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry Max', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 4', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5 ZE620KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.8, 24 mm, 1/2.55, 1.4 µm, PDAF) + 8 MP (f/2.0, 12 mm, 1/4, 1.12 µm), phase detection autofocus, gyro EIS, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Juice A1 Plus Q4260', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Juice Q3551', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Harry', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View XL', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad TipTop N1', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Libero 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.8, 1/2.6-inch Senesr Size, 1.4 μm Pixel Size'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0, 1/3.2 Sensor Size, 1.4-µm Pixel Size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO ZP720', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4 KitKat'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D1', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Max Blue LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P6', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P3', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Tempo X', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BL5000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX362 12MP + Samsung S5K3P9SN 16MP (125° Ultra-wide-angle)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Samsung S5K3P9SP04 16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A711', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 88 Degree Wide Angle Selfie'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'AGM STONE 5S', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4.2 KitKat Operating System'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro C1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO SPEED 8', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow Operating System'}
{'device_name': 'Geotel G1 Terminator', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Prime 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo R1', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X1', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13+13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Small Dolphin 2', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color S5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop up to Marshmallow 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Elyt e1', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO S8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.8 Aperture, CMOS Sensor, Interpolated resolution 8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': '360 OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A2', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense T5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 1.127um Pixel Size, 0.14 inch Sensor Size, F2.4 Aperture, Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo color C3', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with AF and LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with LED Flash, 2P Lens and Aperture F/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad TipTop N1S', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Zenith 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H11', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Detection, f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Sky 3 S', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF and Dual-LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F/2.8 Aperture, LED Flash, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H11', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P5', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': '360 Q5 Plus', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 1.12um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview S6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Elyt e7', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash, 4P Lens, Hynix Hi-553 CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Power', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H11 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with F/2.8 Aperture, LED Flash, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO S8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 3.0MP Sony Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': '360 Q5', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 1.12um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': '360 F4', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 5.1 Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua S3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, 3P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single LED Flash, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat with Amigo UI'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1X', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F/2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Note 5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel With AF and Single LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': '360 F4S', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S50', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO Hero 2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmalow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A10', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions 3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL12000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 88 & 130 Degree Wide Angle Lens,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Hero C2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad 5380CA', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color M5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with 76.1 Degree Wide Angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Power IV', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.4, LED Flash, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee V', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 21 Megapixel 21 Megapixels + 21 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F3', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Tiptop N2M', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color X5.5i 3G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 76.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X60L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Style 3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Speed X', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with OmniVision OV12830 CMOS BSI 2 Sensor, LED Flash, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Rainbow 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F1', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Note', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview S6', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R9', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.8 and LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO Speed 7 (ZP951) Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Note Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (SW 16 Megapixels) Sony Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (SW 16 Megapixels) with 50mA soft flashlight'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash G5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 3P Lens, Aperture F2.2, Hynix Hi-553 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad TipTop Air', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua 5.5 VR+', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Cloud Style 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels SW 8.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Blackberry DTEK50', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual Tone LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84˚ wide angle, 1.125um pixel size, f2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X18', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 50mA soft flashlight, 5P Lens, Samsung Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color C5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 2P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Elyt E6', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X18 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels (SW 20.0MP) f/2.2+ 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2 (SW 13.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Cloud Q11 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone H1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Neon', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual Tone LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84˚ wide angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Defiant', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Note 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 80.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Amaze+', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color C5i', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels LED Flash, 2P Lens,F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes 8 Megapixel with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Pegasus 5S', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture, 85 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua S9 PRO', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ1 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels f/2.0, 25mm with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel f/2.0, 22mm, 1/3 sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Canvas 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Sky 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Shoot 2', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee x10', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X20L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 86 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X30L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Young 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Aperture F2.8, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Aperture F2.4, 90 Degree Wide Angle Lens, OmniVision OV8865 Sensor, LED Flash, 720p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 3', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad M7', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Pegasus 4S Max Plus', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels withBeauty Mode, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with Zen UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Prelude 4G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X30', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool S1', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture,OmniVision OV8856 Sensor, Wideangle lens 84°'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 6', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Pegasus 4S', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels withBeauty Mode, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with Zen UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color M4', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X20', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 86 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Strong 5.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Vantage', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Fancy Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Splatter', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Bro', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Mini High 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, 5P Lens, F2,0 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Trend Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture, 2P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Note 5 Lite C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall T9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Aperture F2.0, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Snap 4', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 8 MP with f/2.2 Aperture, 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Rio', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Torino S2', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Vision 3', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 6', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 1 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus M7S', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 6C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels with 120 Degree Wide Angle, F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On7 Prime (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 1 (C103)', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D2', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview E7s', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P2', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P2 lite', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P600S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P550s', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy S550', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy S500E', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H550S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E520 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy 400 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 2 Q402', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 Megapixel Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel (SW 5.0MP) Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia R1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS (Upgradeable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Evok Note E453', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11 Life', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 1080p, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 8 Megapixel with LED-tone flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Mix S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Evok Power Q4260', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Tough Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pulsemix', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 2S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.2 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia R1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS (Upgradeable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Avid 4', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A7 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP + 2 MP, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 2 Q4310', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11+', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/1.7, 1.4 µm, Dual Pixel PDAF), phase detection autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone V V520KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (f/2.0, 1/2.6, 1.0 µm), phase detection & laser autofocus, 4-axis OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia H8541', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S11S', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 8 Megapixel with LED-tone flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel + 8 Megapixel Front'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 1.4 µm), autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee X', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel Dual'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P6000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 0.33 Megapixels f/2.0 Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max Plus (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/2.0, 35mm) + 8 MP (17mm, no AF), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 25mm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Camera (20MP + 8MP) Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'FunTouch OS 3.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Iconia Talk S', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/1.8, 1.12 µm) + 5 MP, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (1/4), autofocus, 1080p, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview S8', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 0.3MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 0.3 Dual Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y67A', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera with Soft Light Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X4+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP rear camera with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP front-facing camera, 100-degree wide-angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S11 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel with LED-tone flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y79', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 Powered Android 7.1.2'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A520C', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Umidigi Z2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP Dual LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia R1 (Plus)', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, predictive phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, predictive phase detection autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Selfie 2 Q4311', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 1/4), LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with GalaxyCore GC5025 CMOS Sensor, F2.2 Aperture, 76.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG U', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels f/2.2 Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.2 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS Powered (Android 7.1.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K5', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y65', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 Powered Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 13 Megapixel Rear Camera with AF & LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y66i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S30', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X1', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with GalaxyCore GC5025 CMOS Sensor, F2.2 Aperture, 76.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Infinity', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3, 1.12 µm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, LED flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat), planned upgrade to Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 03MP ( SW 13MP + 8MP ) Dual Front cameras with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y75', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 Powered Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S30 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo P5000', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 1.109um Pxel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Harmony', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Force', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP, phase detection autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot KingKong', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Selfie 2 Note Q4601', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 1/4), LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P8w', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'VIVO Y53', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu mBlu S6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android N'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 23 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels+5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, 3P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Mix2', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels) f/2.0 CMOS sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (1/3, 1.12 µm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Amigo OS 3.5 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo 5000', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 1.109um Pxel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Mini S', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels+5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A7', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (f/2.0, 1/3), phase detection autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11 Eyes', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Madrid', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Prelude Plus', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10B', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels+ 5MP (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q8', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (28mm, f/1.8, 1/2.6, laser AF, OIS) + 8 MP (10mm, f/2.4, 1/4, no AF), laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/1.9, 1/5, 1.12 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Elife S8', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Mega Pixel Camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee James Bond 2', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10C', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu MX', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 2.3.5 (Gingerbread), upgradeable to 4.0 (Ice Cream Sandwich)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A6 Premium', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Atom', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP+2MP with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 5', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3, 1.12 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.4, 1/5, 1.12 µm), 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee A1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 10 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.2, 28mm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.8, 34mm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F106', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Mirror 5s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Allcall Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels +2MP with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M5', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Mega Pixel Camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P Smart', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 2 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F109L', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8C', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F109', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S9', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.1 (Nougat) operating system'}
{'device_name': 'Allcall Rio S', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP (f/2.0, 1/2.4), OIS, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu T10', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3MP'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Overture 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee W909', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Mega Pixel Camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A39', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.2, 1/3), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.4, 1/4, 1.4 µm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 2+', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F5 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (f/2.0, 2.0 µm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C9', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 21MP back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'OV8858 8MP front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Pioneer P5L', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu T18', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0 Sony IMX219PC Exmor R Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee X1', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S11', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP + 5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A330', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A4', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'OV8858 8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F6', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels, + 2 MP (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6s', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP camera, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No Data'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Pioneer P5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Fanfare 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 3 Q437', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'THL Knight 2', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S5', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone Fighter', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'OV8858 8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Pro (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED-flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 4 Q440', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 5', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, (Expected)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Camera, (16MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, up to 4128 x 3096-pixel pictures, HDR, autofocus, Geo-tagging, panorama camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2MP, up to 1600 x 1200-pixel pictures'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 KitKat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Selfie 3 Q460', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F103B', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry DTEK60', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A2', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, + 2 MP (Dual Cameras)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo), (Expected)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Dual 4 E4816', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (1/3)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Dual-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F100', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Keyone', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.0, 1/2.3, 1.55 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 1.12 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 6s', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3, 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus, dual-LED'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.2, 31mm), 1080p@30fps, 720p@240fps, face detection, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 9, upgradable to iOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S20', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1X', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 2 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 3D', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F306', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop with Amigo UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Motion', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus, dual-LED'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 1.125 um), 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu M6', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Infinity Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP (f/2.0) + 8 MP (f/2.2)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 6s Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3, 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus, OIS, Dual-LED'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.2, 31mm), 1080p@30fps, 720p@240fps, face detection, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 9, upgradable to iOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13MP Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F100S', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow with Amigo UI 3.5'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 4 Selfie ZD553KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, 26mm, gyro EIS, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 20 MP (f/2.0, 31mm) + 8 MP (12mm), LED flash, panorama, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U5 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP+5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z520', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo Mate 10', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony 16MP/5MP rear cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP/5MP front cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3, 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.2 MP (f/2.4, 31mm), 720p@30fps, face detection, HDR, FaceTime over Wi-Fi or Cellular'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 9.3.2, upgradable to iOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi R1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 4 Max ZC520KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Dual 5', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One X10', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (f/2.0, 26mm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 23mm, 1.12 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 4 Max Plus ZC554KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom 6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon C9', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS V1.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A8 US Version', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X20', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0 (IMX386)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-cameras: 16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor E', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13.0MP) LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel ( SW 5.0MP ) Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K5000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels Sony IMX135 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel (Interpolated 21MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A8 SE', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Boom J8', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Hi OS (Android 5.1 Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Active', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels Sony Sensor Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 6 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S9', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C8 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon C7', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 1.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans Note 4', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Little Pepper S11', 'manufacturer': 'Little Pepper', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno W4', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 1.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X1 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17S', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 (IMX362) + 23 MP, f/2.0 (IMX318)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K320T', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Rear 8+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K3', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 2 Megapixels with Dual LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17 miniS', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S60', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview R6', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee X1s', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8+ (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Single 16 Megapixel with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 8MP Dual Front Camera with F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 (OV16880)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon CX', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels Dual Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon CX Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee MIX 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.0 (IMX 258) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno L9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix 2 Silver', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/2.0 Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 8 Megapixel f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A75S', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with LED-flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 3.2 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Single 16 Megapixel with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 8MP Dual Front Camera with F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y66', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L2', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3.1), autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.4, 1/4), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S30', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A75', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with LED-flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 3.2 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q6', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7 + 5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y67', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S10', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 (IMX219)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA2 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (f/2.0, 24mm, 1/2.3), phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/2.0, 23mm, 1/2.6, OIS, AF) + 8 MP (f/2.4, 1/4)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL12000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+8MP Dual Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Essential PH-1', 'manufacturer': 'Essential', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Dual RGB) + 13 MP (Mono), f/1.85'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Dula-LED and AF Dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 4.0 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A83', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with LED-flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 (IMX219)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA2', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (f/2.0, 24mm, 1/2.3), phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/2.0, 23mm, 1/2.6, OIS, AF) + 8 MP (f/2.4, 1/4)'}, 'operating_system': 'Google Android™ O'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 7s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13+2 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL12000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+8MP Dual Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S8', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.3 (Kitkat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/2.0 Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 8 Megapixel f/2.2 Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X20 Plus UD', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A7', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': '360 N6 Lite', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': '360 N6', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A8 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Tab 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon M', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP. f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M9', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP+2MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+2MP Dual Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 Lite (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': '360 N6 Pro', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+2MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16+15MP Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13+15MP Dual Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K8000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-cameras: 16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno I3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Quad LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED & Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo KIICAA Power', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot H3', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP & 3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP, f/2.0 (IMX376) + 8MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP | 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld S8', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Tab 4', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Rear Camera With Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M7', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A79', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno W3 LTE Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M5 Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 6.0(Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11S', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/1.7 + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 12 MP, f/1.6 (Both), w/ OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HP Pro 8', 'manufacturer': 'HP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/1.7 + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': '360 F5', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel f/1.8 Sony Rear Camera with AF & LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (Mono) + 12 MP (RGB), f/1.6 (w/ OIS)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense A2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 2S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 20 MP f/1.8 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 2 MP f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 (OV16880)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Razer Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.75 + 12 MP f/2.6'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-cameras: 16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A6', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V9 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P9000', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone V', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 2 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan U2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0 (x2)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat), Current: Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M5', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2 Max', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels+21 Megapixels with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel With AF and Single-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K8', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A1Q', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A77', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K8 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan U1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat), Current: Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan T2', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (IMX258) + 5 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) | Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat (Upgradable Up to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan T1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG V10', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K6', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel + 2 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel Dual'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A71', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 6A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone X', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 + 12 MP, f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A2S', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 + 12 MP, f/2.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Gemini Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) + 13 MP (Mono), f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+2MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 8', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + 12 MP f/2.6'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo S8', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 10 Lite (Maimang 6)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Notebook Pro 15.6″ (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Windows 10 (Home Version)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.6 (Telephoto) + 12 MP, f/1.8 (Wide-Angle Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 12 MP f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo S1', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M5c', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Z4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Tizen 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) + 13 MP (Mono)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Front)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.6 + 13 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Z2 Force', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (Mono) + 12 MP (RGB), f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A7', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (S5K4E2), f/2.4 + 0.3 MP (GC0310), f/2.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP (GC2385)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenPad Z8 (ZT581KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld Mix Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 3 (8) LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Pegasus 3', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.6 + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T1', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP f/2.0 (S5K3P3) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Maze Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (6)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP (f/2.6, AF) + 16 MP (f/1.7, PDAF), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Magic', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.4 + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackberry Aurora', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A8', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (IMX149)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T5', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 7 (Chang Xiang 7)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB), f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (6) 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo KIICAA Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 216', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (7)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 ZE520KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo M1', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP + 8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K6000 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Fierce XL (Windows)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 230 Dual SIM', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 480p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 2 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U16 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6000s', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 (IMX219)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP (OV2680)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z2 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1.4 µm pixel size, dual-LED (dual tone) flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 230', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 480p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo S8', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Rear) +'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 16 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Secondary 20 MP & 5 MP f/2.0 (w/ LED Flash)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Laser ZC551KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV7000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI Crystal', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 6 (2014)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat), 5.1.1 (Lollipop), Possible Upgrade 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4s', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 16 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Secondary 20 MP & 5 MP f/2.0 (w/ LED Flash)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV7000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld S3', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto E4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (NA) | Android 7.1.1 (Intl.)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X venture', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note FE', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB452KG', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP or 8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA, f/2.8 or 2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld T2', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z11', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 24 mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV4000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Max ZC520TL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, LED flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto E4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (NA) | Android 7.1.1 (Intl.)'}
{'device_name': '360 N5S', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, F / 2.0 aperture, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF , 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld F2', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (Sony IMX149)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense H10', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (RGB) f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung J7+', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7 + 5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'YotaPhone 3', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A77 (MT Edition)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4s Windows', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto C Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.8, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G5S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP (Sony IMX230)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (Samsung S5K3P3)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, phase detection autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto C', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (Samsung S5K3P3)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.0 + ? MP (Wide-angle) f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 4', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G5S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenPad 3S 10 (Z500M)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y69', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenPad Z10 (ZT500KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K3', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 4 plus', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL5000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2 (x2)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7 + 12 MP, f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'YotaPhone 2', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.1 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 8 MP, f/1.75'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Deluxe 5.5 ZS550KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 + 23 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.6 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool M7', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 4S', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Pro (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Leader 8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto X4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Max ZC553KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection & laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB450KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.9 + 5 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel POP 7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone Go (ZB551KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP or 13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV8000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (Telephoto) f/2.6 + 16 MP (Wide-angle) f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu E2', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone Go (T500)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB500KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 5A (S)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max ZC550KL 2016', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 5S', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + 12 MP f/2.6'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (Mono) + 12 MP (RGB), f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenPad 3S 10 LTE (Z500KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ1 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 ZE552KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 12 MP (Mono) f/2.0 + 12 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone Go (ZC451TG)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Max', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL7000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (x2)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Deluxe ZS570KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 7', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 12 MP (Mono) f/2.0 + 12 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le 1s', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop) - LeEco Le 1s | Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) - LeEco Le 1s Eco'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB552KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Live (G500TG)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP f/2.2 + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 Selfie Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (x2) f/1.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Flash 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 8 MP + 5 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 2 Laser ZE551KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Ultra ZU680KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi First', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Fierce 4', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Zoom ZX551ML', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.7-4.8, 28-84mm (3x optical zoom), laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) f/2.2 + 13 MP (Monochrome) - IMX258 Sensors'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 3C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel X1', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1/4 sensor size, 1.4 µm pixel size, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Flash 2', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZC500TG', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (5)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max ZC550KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Fierce XL', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 3 (5)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP or 8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP/ 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 3 (5.5)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP | 8 MP | 13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP | 5 MP | 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0, 25mm, EIS (gyro), predictive phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 22mm, 1/3 sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia N2', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, F2.2 , PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, F2.0, 5-piece lens, Super beauty skin 2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto M', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1/4 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZs', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0, 25mm, EIS (gyro), predictive phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 22mm, 1/3 sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F5', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Flash Plus 2', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One M9s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1/4 sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 828 dual sim', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 6', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (Telephoto) + 12 MP (Wide-Angle Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1/4 sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 active', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection & laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, auto-HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), planned upgrade to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Pro3 Elite', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 728 dual sim', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A57', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P8 Lite (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One E9s dual sim', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Pro 3 AI', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, f/2.0, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 630', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.4, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 3 G389F', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S6s', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 Mp + 12 MP, F/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, F/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Huawei EMUI 5.0 (compatible with Android 7.0)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J Max', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Express Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 2MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab J', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 4X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A3 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 825', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A5 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 27mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Grand Prime Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M5S', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC ONE ME（M9et）', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A5 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, 24mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 526', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A3 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3310 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NIL'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'HTC 10 Lifestyle', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm, OIS, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.8, 23mm,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F103 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A7 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, 24mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenPad 3 8.0 (Z581K)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 626s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 24mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One S9', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Pegasus 3s', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A7 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 27mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J1 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One M9 Prime Camera', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J1 Nxt', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB690KG', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP or 8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Emerge', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S9', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 5MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 USA', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 626 USA', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 628', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4, 28mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Zoom ZE553KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, (25mm, f/1.7, OIS (4-axis) & 59mm, f/2.8), 2.3x zoom, laser/phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 1/3 sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 edge USA', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J1 mini prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop) - 3G model | Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) - LTE model'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P7', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X style', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G6', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP (f/1.8, OIS, 3-axis) + 13 MP (f/2.4), laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia M2', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 13 MP, F2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, F2.0, 80 degrees wide angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone AR ZS571KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, OIS (4-axis), 3x zoom, depth & motion tracking sensors, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': '360 N5', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android, 6.0 ( Marshmallow )'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 Plus Power', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One A9s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 33.7 mm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 12 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X power', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus | 8 MP, autofocus, - LS755, US610, K450'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Shine Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y55s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP + 12 MP, f/2.2, OIS, Leica optics, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Pro (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Holly 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 10 Lifestyle', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G Pad X 8.0', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee A1', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Pad 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C5', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G Pad III 8.0 FHD', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5c', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2, 27mm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 27mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee A1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 5 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0, 1/2.8 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A3 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 650', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Steel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Mach', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.3 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab S3 9.7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 27mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 23mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, F/2.2 + 13 MP (Monochrome), MX258 RGB Sensor + IMX258 Mono Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5II', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X power2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X max', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A3', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC 10 Evo', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, OIS,PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, 1080p, Auto-HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8+', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAf, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7, autofocus, 1440p@30fps, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y3II', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A5 LED', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Butterfly 3', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 MP Duo, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, 2160p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop), planned upgrade to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 5C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3s Max ZC521TL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot CHEETAH 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP ( 16.0MP ) with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( 13.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Skin', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'UMI Plus E', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'UMi Z', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP,with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Live ZB501KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One A9', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size, 1080p@30fps, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia M2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, F2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, F2.0, 80 degrees wide angle, Super beauty skin 2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U5', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U Play', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei G9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, OIS, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G Pad III 10.1 FHD', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 4X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm, OIS, laser & PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, 1080p, Auto-HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, - J3109, J320F | 5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, - J320P, J320A,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 720p@30fps - J3109, J320F | 2 MP - J320P, J320A'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M2017', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP + 13 MP, 2x optical zoom, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia X Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, 24mm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), planned upgrade to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, OIS, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K3 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, 24mm, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 23mm, autofocus, 1/4 sensor size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab E 8.0', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA1 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, 24mm, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 23mm, 1/2.6 sensor size, OIS, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K4 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab A 10.1 (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2, 1080p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Marathon M5 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylus 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab A 7.0 (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S8', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1/4 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 728 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 530', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0,PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One X9', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X6S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V3Max', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Holly 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1/4 sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 2A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 6', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.75 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 1.0 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 5 Elite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F1s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 1/3.1 sensor size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A59', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 4 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.8, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.3 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 6X (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP + 2 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X6S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vkworld T1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP,with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 6', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld G1', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP,with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( SW 13.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP ) front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.1, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.3'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1/4 sensor size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview R7', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X5 Max +', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo Maya Max', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 10 pro', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Vibe K5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On5', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP (Interpolation to 12.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP (Interpolation to 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP +20.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 6S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Vibe K5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 7', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/1.8, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z11 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, 1080p, 1.4 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y55', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Vibe K4 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X5 Max Platinum Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP +12 MP, f/2.2, OIS, 2x zoom, phase detection & laser autofocus, Leica optics.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia N1', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS U100', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP（SW13.0MP）'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP（SW5.0MP）'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K7000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP ) with flashlight'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP ( SW 5.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP with flashlight and auto focus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Warp 7', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y37', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 9 Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP +12 MP, f/2.2, OIS, 2x zoom, Leica optics, phase detection & laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Z3 Corporate Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Tizen 2.4'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP, with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K6000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( Interpolation to 13.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP ( Interpolation to 5.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'MEIZU PRO 6s', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS H5000', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( SW 13.0 MP ) with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y35', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE ZMAX Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2-2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Phab2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP PDAF , depth and motion tracking sensors'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M2 note', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 7 mini', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y31', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS U200', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP（SW13.0MP）'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP（SW5.0MP）'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 1080p (1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan M1L', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0 (IMX318)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0 (OV4688)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Phab2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, f/2.0, laser & PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Pro-2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu MX5e', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z11 mini S', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan M1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23MP, f/2.0 (IMX318)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4MP, f/2.0 (OV4688)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V1 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 4i', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Base: Android 5.0.2 (Lollipop) Latest: Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu U20', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android operating system'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu U10', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android operating system'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu X', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, Ƒ / 2.0, PDAF, 6-piece lens'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, Ƒ / 2.0, 5-piece lens, ArcSoft beauty algorithm Adaptive skin technology, Face AE Intelligent adjustment of facial brightness.'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme based Android 6 (Up gradable to Flyme 6)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z11 Mini S', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus X', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 2 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat), upgradable to 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual camera with PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'TBA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 2', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.1, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M1 Metal', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M5 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus One', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (KitKat), upgradable to (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Bolt', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '18 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 10800p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo ZUK Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 million effective pixels 1.34 μm large pixels Samsung custom ISOCELL pixel grille image sensor Aperture: f / 2.2 large aperture Lens components: 5P Focus range: 10cm to infinity PDAF + CAF double focus mode, the fastest 0.1 seconds focus Qualcomm 14-bit Spectra ™ isp High-brightness flash One-touch short video recording, face detection, panoramic mode Intelligent HDR, time to take pictures 960fps slow motion video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1.12μm large pixels, Aperture: f / 2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 4c', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K4000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP (Interpolation to 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP (Interpolation to 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo ZUK Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R9s Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP, Sony IMX 398'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M3 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, Ƒ / 2.0 Large aperture blur, Sony IMX386 CMOS, PDAF, Laser Focus.'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, Ƒ / 2.0, 5-piece lens, ArcSoft beauty skin adaptive algorithm technology, Face AE Intelligent .'}, 'operating_system': 'Flyme based Android 6 (Up gradable to Flyme 6)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.3 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone ZOOM', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo ZUK Z2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP (SW 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP (SW 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Z2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Tizen 2.4'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M5', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo ZUK Z2', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS A101S', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( SW 13.0MP ) with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP ( SW 5.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K4000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP (SW13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front 2.0MP (SW5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'MEIZU M3S', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP,with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M3', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 3T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le S3', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U15 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP ( SW 16.0MP）'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP ( SW 5.0MP）'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M3E', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL U10', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZENFONE 3', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'MEIZU PRO 6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Neo 7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP + 2.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C9', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A37', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4, 1/4 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U15S', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP ( SW 16.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu m3 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu MX6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), Current: Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On7 – 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo X9', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP AF with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld T6', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R9s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP, Sony IMX 398'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP, f/2.0 (IMX376)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Pad 7.9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, with PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP + 8 MP, 1080p, 1/2.8 sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'SONY E6883 Xperia Z5', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 4A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, Autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': '360 N4s', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, with PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP + 8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo Picasso', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( interpolated to 13.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( interpolated to 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG LV5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC 10', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 830', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO Maya', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Andriod 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP, F2.0, 1/2.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm (wide), AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.2 '}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y15S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO XTOUCH', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8 -2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': '360 N4A', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT X10', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X6', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y11', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL U10', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y51', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X5 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP,f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 5', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S7', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 16.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.3 (KitKat), Current: 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': '360 N4', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP, Sony IMX398'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE F3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 13.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP (Interpolation To 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 3', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P9000 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 13.0MP OV13850'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE Y300', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 8.0MP ( SW 13.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Z100', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 8.0MP ( SW 13.0MP）'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 5.0MP ( SW 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P9000', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear camera: Sony IMX258 13MP F/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: OV8858 8MP 84° wide angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE Y100X', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 8.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 5MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 - Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE DG700', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 8.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 16.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT S600', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 13.0MP ( SW16.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP ( SW8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Pad 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0/ Windows 10 (64 GB Model)'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE F5', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 13.0 MP (SW16.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP(SW8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP, Sony IMX378, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4MP'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI 8 base on Android'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear camera: 13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT NOTE S', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 5.0MP (SW8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 2.0MP (SW5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Umi Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP with two-tone flashlight and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP, f/2.0, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), Current: Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'UMI Touch', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Rainbow', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 8.0MP (SW 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 2.0MP (SW 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE X5 MAX Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front-camera: 5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG G3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes, 2.1 MP, 1080p@30fps, video call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'UMI Super', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 - Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Umi Max', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE X5 MAX', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front-camera: 5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S4 Zoom', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes, 1.9 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.2.2 (Jelly Bean), upgradable to v4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Max', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 8.0MP (Interpolated 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 1.3MP (Interpolated 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes, 2.1 MP, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (kitkat)'}
{'device_name': 'HUAWEI Mate 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 4S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 - Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'HUAWEI Mate 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One (E8)', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 10800p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X16 S', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 8.0MP (SW 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0 (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Future', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rare camera: 16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Rare camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X16', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP ( interpolated 16.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP ( interpolated 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP, with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Paris', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rare: 13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front: 5.0 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 3X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT H1', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 8.0MP (interpolated 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP(interpolated 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes, 1.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'CUBOT Dinosaur', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 8.0MP ( Interpolation to 13.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 2.0MP ( Interpolation to 5.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Be Touch 3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL C2', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP （interpolated to 5.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP （interpolated to 5.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia Lumia 930', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 mega pixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes, 1.2 MP, 720p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows Phone 8.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0 - , 1/3 sensor size, 2µm pixel size, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X17', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 13.0MP ( interpolated 16.0MP )'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP ( interpolated 8.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K10000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP (SW 13.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP (SW 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Vienna', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rare camera: 13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Androrid 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Pro 3', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel, Sony IMX298, PDAF, F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel, F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X15', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 16.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8000', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear:13MP Samsung 3L2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front:5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K6000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP (SW 16.0MP) with Dual flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Mono) + 13 MP (RGB)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rare: 16GB ROM'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'iPhone 7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.0MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS10'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Mars', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera 13.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'iPhone 7', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.0 MP,f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 10'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP, Sony IMX389'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone M3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear:21MP (Sony IMX 230)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front:8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 - Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera 8.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera 2.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le 2', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 8.0MP,f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual, 20MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear Camera: OV8856 13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 2MP F/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 3S Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone M2', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear camera: SONY IMX214 13MP F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': '64-bit / Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear Camera: 21MP 6P, f/2.0 for 4K video'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front Camera: 1.4μm 8MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG V20', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8 + 8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE X6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 2.0MP (SW 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'LG G5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Rear:Sony IMX135 13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front:5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE X6', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back-camera: 5.0MP (SW 8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 2.0MP (SW 5.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23MP, f/2.0 (Sony IMX318)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 6X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual, 12MP & 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'DOOGEE Y100 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Back camera: 13.0MP,with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Front camera: 8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
